Hello, everyone
YING HA. YING HA.
I did a musical during the day and turned on the live broadcast
Today is a very special day for me and Lovelinus
Today is LOVELYZ's 9th anniversary
9 years! It's already been 9 years since Lovelyz
chan oppa, we will rock you go ahead
Let 'we will rock' have a nightlife! (you hung = nightlife)
It's our 9th anniversary, so we turned on this live broadcast
I put on makeup, and it's been hours, so my makeup has collapsed a lot, but please understand.
Please understand.
I'm not hungry, but why is my stomach rumbling?
So today, I'm going to celebrate my birthday in a self-congratulatory style.
They gave it to me in front of the musical.
It's...
They gave me this glass.
I can't alcohol right now, so I'll pour the drink.
It's not alcohol.
It's a drink.
Congratulations on your 9th anniversary.
It's delicious
Even if I drink a glass like this, will it feel like I'm drinking champagne?
It's not doping for Bae_ten.
Did you enjoy "Hibjiro Office Worker"? Thank you.
I saw it at the end, too.
I'm back in the world of idols.
There were two endings.
So one is Ye-In who is going back to her life as an idol
"Ye-In who stays at work." There were two versions
Ye-In's version that's left at work was also filmed.
I filmed the ending with Jungwoo going home.
Yes, anyway
Won't they upload the leftover cookies?
Yeah, it would be nice if you could post it as a cookie.
There was originally an ending to work.
Time flies so fast. 9 years is like that
It's been 9 years since I've been with Lovelyz in my teens and 20s
It's so creepy. I feel like I'm a grandmother all of a sudden
Whenever I go somewhere these days, people tell me that they're enjoying Bae_ten's performance
Why do I feel so embarrassed whenever I hear that I'm watching Bae_ten well
I've shown you a lot of bad things in Bae_ten
I guess I'm a bit embarrassed thinking that you saw it
The light is so
Be dazzling.
If I turn it off, it'll be too dark
In that case
At times like this
What should I do?
Should I turn that on?
What about this, everyone
I think it's like this
I think this is better
What do you think
Nina, do you still like hearing the youngest sound
By all means.
I feel like I'm young. I'm happy because I feel that way
It sounds good.
I want you to come to Japan
I recently went to Japan
I went there because I had to do this and that
The weather is so nice
I'm so happy
It was so nice
There might be new people coming in right now
This is not alcohol
It's a drink
It's not pear juice
It's a Sanpele Grino drink
Is the taxi fare real
I know. I missed the shuttle bus
It was about 260,000 won for a taxi
It was really sad
I didn't ride it for an hour or even an hour. I didn't ride a taxi for an hour
The taxi fare got hit by a bomb
I was so sad
I'll take the shuttle bus
What's that
Yeah, just buy the hoodie you want to buy
It's 260,000 won, so I'll pay for the taxi
I went to the airport with tears in my eyes
I went to the airport again
Narita Airport opens at 8 o'clock
So I couldn't find the store that opened, so I ate Shin Ramen at the convenience store
a true story
Anyway, I went to do that musical today
Many fans congratulated me on my 9th anniversary
I was so happy
I'm feeling cheerful.
Oh, the 9th anniversary
Congratulations on your 9th anniversary
Thank you, oppa
It's been a while since I talked to the older members
That's what happened
I didn't get in touch with the members that I didn't get in touch with often
in celebration of each other
I contacted him
That's right. Hun Sua came to watch the musical today, too
It felt so good to see Mamiruda for the first time in a while
She grew up a lot
Ye-In is in a good mood today. That's right
I feel good
Right, I think there were as many fans as the first song
You like me since 4 years of elementary school, and now you are in 3nd grade of high school?
Wow, you'll become an adult soon
I was so excited when I became an adult
but, it's not much different when you're an adult, is it?
Ye-In, I went to the Cheongeun Literature Library yesterday. It's really nice. That's right
I feel like I can read books that I've never read before
I remember watching Lovelyz on "Weekly Idol"
Isn't Mi-Joo the MC for "Weekly Idol"?
I'm so proud of you
I don't play LoL
I'm not good at games
I don't know how to play games
I'm not good at games.
You're going to watch it next week?
Yes, come and watch it
It's fun. Musical
I didn't feel good when I became an adult
failed the SAT.
It's okay. The test can fail.
Our lives are not ruined
Is it possible for Yang Yein right now...
What's Yang Ye-in?
What is Yang Ye-in?
Do you eat a lot?
Okay, eat a lot
pigtails
Since I did pigtails in the musical
Rather than pigtails
I like hair with dumplings on both sides
You don't know how comfortable this hair is, do you?
If you do this, it's really comfortable
It's not annoying
It's gotten really cold these days, right
I remember we debuted when it was this cold
As far as I remember, we had a showcase at YES24
I went to see the fan concert yesterday?
A teacher who plays the role of Galileo
They had a fan concert
I went to YES24 again
It reminded me of the past
I was like this, but what if I didn't do it at YES24?
Was it at Blue Square?
I think I did it at YES24. Anyway
Oh? You had your debut showcase at Olympic Park?
Where did we have our debut showcase, Lovelyz?
I think it was YES24?
Don't you remember because it's been so long?
Anyway
It's very
It reminded me of this. I recently watched some Lovelyz diaries.
I saw it, and I think that fresh feeling disappears only when it's not that time.
I'm so thankful that it was recorded then.
I'm at home right now, everyone.
We're getting old together, really. We're getting old together.
Season's greeting concept spoiler?
It's not fun to give spoilers.
I went to the shop. I had a musical during the day.
Lovelyz in Wonderland. Lovelyz in Wonderland was fun too.
Now that I think about it, the fact that we filmed a reality program with our names on it
I think it was a great and thankful thing.
I had a lot of fun filming it. I'm still in touch with the producers I worked with
I had a lot of fun filming it.
Canada that LOVELYZ loved?
That was really nice in Canada.
It was so nice, Canada.
Of course, the members talked about our 9th anniversary.
Of course I did.
As soon as the comments said Ye-In has good physical strength
I'm yawning so tired just now.
I think my physical strength has gotten a lot worse.
For the past 9 years
Thank you for being by my side
Thank you so much, Linus
I'll be a Linus for the rest of my life
I'll be LOVELYZ forever
Have you eaten your dinner?
No, not yet
I'm hungry
I don't think I'm used to the daytime performances yet
I can't wake up
Anyway, it's our 9th anniversary
9th anniversary
Let's say congratulations again
Oh, yes. The sound right now is the sound of the washing machine
I'm running the washing machine right now
In a little while
But since I just turned it on
Speaking of dinner, Do you remember eating salad during the live broadcast?
Ramen is so
I ate a small ramen for a long time
Who's going to refill the ramen from the bottom?
I ate a small ramen for too long
I'm still slow to eat
But I've been eating a lot lately
When I was in a musical
I gained a lot of weight while watching how I lost weight
I think I gained about 1 or 2kg
I don't have a scale at home
I don't know exactly how much I weigh
I think I lost 1 or 2kg
I think I gained weight
Wow, but
If your eye body is okay, it's okay
I think the eye body is more important
When I measure my body
I don't really like it
I don't feel good
When I measure my in-body
Don't you feel bad
My eye body feels bad, too
It's so funny
I don't think I'm that close to working out
I do it when I do, but I don't think I like it
Thank you. Happy 9th anniversary, RINUS
Yes, the glasses don't have any lenses. These are fashion glasses
It's our 9th anniversary
But it's such a shame not to do live, right?
Do I look younger with glasses?
Do I look smart?
What's the thing that makes you look smart?
Do I look like a smart kid?
Can you be friends with someone born in 2009? Of course, I can
I don't have anything like that
I'm consoling you because I'm like friends with you
It doesn't matter if the younger members treat you like that
Does it feel different when you wear glasses? Are your eyes half closed?
Okay, let's be friends. Let's be friends
You can just call me "unni oppa"
You have to relax your mind and do that
You think I can fly around in the Kkotto Show with these glasses?
Do you call your brother or uncle who is 15 years older than you?
brother
HYOIN is here, too
I don't know if they came in or if they pressed the wrong button
Anyways, everyone
I'm very hungry
I was a bit sleepy
Should I just sleep without eating? Should I eat or not? What would be good?
Do you think it would be embarrassing to do a live broadcast in front of your family?
No, I'm not embarrassed at all
I'm not embarrassed at all
I'm thinking that there's only Lovelinus here
It's carbonated
I don't fill up the amount
There's ji youn
Congratulations on your 9th anniversary
Is the purple pajama from the picture you posted today?
I'm still wearing pants. Purple pajamas
This is a pajama brand called Prinkly Sleepy
My YouTube...
If you go to Ye-In's YouTube channel, I've explained everything
Let me tell you again what it tastes like
It's not alcohol
Just.
It's a drink
What's wrong with my hair?
I woke up this morning and the weather was so cold
So I thought, "What would I have done if I didn't have a robe at home?"
I went to the musical with the heating on. I came home and it was so warm and I felt really good
I didn't go on a trip to Japan, but I couldn't film YouTube
But the weather was so cold yesterday. I thought I was going to freeze to death on the street
Colds and flu are in vogue these days. Even if you're lazy, make sure to wear a mask
It's sad when you're sick
Anyways, everyone
Congratulations on your 9th anniversary
Congratulations to me, too
Congratulations to all of us
Congratulations
I'll do a live broadcast again soon
Whenever I say "everyone", I feel like I'm going to end the live broadcast
I can turn it on again. Next time
Next time, after the musical
I'm going to wear a live broadcast
As soon as I turned off the live broadcast
I feel like I can fall asleep in a minute
It's sad to go on our 9th anniversary
I'll stay awake a little longer
Congratulations on your 9th anniversary
Thanks to RINUS, I was able to do this much
Thank you for your support
Hi.
Bye, everyone. See you again
Su-Jeong does capture time. Should I try it too
Take a screenshot of me, too
9th anniversary
Bye Bye