VIVIZ High School Welcomes the New School Year of 2024
Kim Ye-won arrives at school - Top student at VIVIZ High School - Seems to have a hidden past.
Teacher: As expected, Ye-won
Arriving first like a model student
Hwang Eun-bi arrives at school - Sophomore class 5's popular girl and cool girl - Loves dancing
Steps gradually slow down for some reason...
Teacher: Hwang Eun-bi, come here
Teacher: Where is Eun-bi's tie?
Teacher: Penalty points for improper attire, 3 points
Teacher: Take care of it
Shinbi: Goodbye
Penalty, 3 points. Hwang Eun-bi arrives at school
Only 5 minutes left until school start time
Run, Eun-bi
Heh / Jung Eun-bi arrives - Cute but clumsy - Sometimes makes sharp criticisms
Teacher: Let's go. If she’s here, everyone should be here.
What will happen at VIVIZ High School?
Classroom for sophomore class 5
Model student Ye-won arrives first
Sitting near the teacher as expected of a model student
Half excitement, half nervousness
Other students gradually arrive too
An awkward air fills the new semester classroom
I want to make friends
At that moment, the door opens
Eun-bi, where did you get that tie?
(Hwang) Eun-bi naturally heads to the back seat
Shinbi: Oh, you’re in class 5 too!
Shinbi: Do you know her?
Shinbi: Hi
Friends exchange shy first greetings
Shinbi: So pretty~
Ha ha ha
Eunha: If I hadn’t had that slice of bread, I wouldn’t have been able to open the door
(Jung) Eun-bi also manages to arrive at school
But the classroom remains silent...
Eunha: Are you by any chance Hwang Eun-bi from Cheonan North Middle School?
Shinbi: Jung Eun-bi from Sinnam Middle School?
Oh my...!
Just heard about you. I’ve heard a lot.
Eunha: You really wanted to be friends, huh?
Shinbi: Do you know her?
Fully focused body
Shinbi: Sistar from Sinsong Middle School
[Huh]
Eunha: Kim Ye-won...! No way, that...that...!
Eunha: The one who danced to 'So Cool'?
Shinbi: She doesn’t dance anymore
(Forgotten past of Sinsong Middle School's Sistar)
Eunha: Is she studying?
Shinbi: Suddenly got her act together in high school
Ye-won: Very proactive.
Shinbi: She’s got some pride
Eunha: Seems a bit conceited too, a bit
Shinbi: She’s reading an English book
Will school life be okay?
Then, the homeroom teacher of Class 2-5 makes an appearance.
Teacher: Everyone is seated very nicely.
Teacher: The class president needs to...
Teacher: There’s no class president.
Shinbi: There's no class president.
Teacher: Should we choose a class president?
Teacher: Should we start by accepting nominations from those who want to run for class president?
Everyone is looking around, hesitant.
Kim Yewon: I volunteer for the class president election.
Teacher: Yewon again?
Friend: I nominate Hwang Eunbi.
Shinbi: Seriously, what's wrong with them?
Shinbi: What's going on?
Teacher: Since Hwang Eunbi is nominated...
Telepathy
Eunha: I, I will also run.
Teacher: Okay, Jeong Eunbi as well.
Teacher: So, we have three candidates.
Teacher: Let's hear their campaign promises, shall we?
Umji: Hello.
Umji: My name is Kim Yewon and,
Umji: given the current situation,
Umji: I will do my best to create a good night atmosphere so that we can focus on our studies this year.
Shinbi: What situation are you talking about?
Failed to immerse.
Umji: I will do my best to create a good environment for studying at night.
Umji: Please support me.
Umji: Thank you.
Shinbi: Wait a second.
Shinbi: I think a campaign promise is where you talk about what you will do.
Shinbi: Isn't it?
Umji: Oh, campaign promises.
Umji: I’ve been taking notes lately,
Umji: and I will share them with friends who need them.
Eunha: Huh?
Eunha: Then, how are your grades?
Shinbi: She was number one in the entire school last year.
In fact, Yewon maintained the number one spot in the entire school last year.
Umji: That’s not true. I didn’t do well in my studies during middle school.
Shinbi: Can I ask something I’m really curious about?
Shinbi: Are you the Sistar from Shinsong Middle School?
And so, the scandalous past is revealed.
Kim Yewon is pretending to be a model student once again.
Shinbi: Was it 'So Cool'?
Umji: No, I never did anything like that.
Shinbi: Aw, that’s boring. I was going to vote for you.
Umji: Anyway, since we’ll be seniors next year,
Umji: I hope everyone will focus on studying. Goodbye!
Exiting while leaving behind massive curiosity, Yewon.
What on earth happened at Shinsong Middle School that year?
SinB: Hi, I'm Hwang Eun Bi.
SinB: *claps*
SinB: Even though we're in the second year of high school,
SinB: I hope we don't take things too seriously.
SinB: If I become the class president,
SinB: I'll get rid of self-study time.
SinB: (looking at the teacher for permission while speaking)
The top student objects.
SinB: This is my time now.
SinB: It's my turn.
SinB: Did you see my leadership?
*overwhelms everyone*
SinB: How about we replace self-study time
SinB: with some free time to do what we want?
Umji: Can we do things other than studying during free time?
SinB: I'll dance.
Ohhh!
Eunha: Oh, then can you show us a dance first?
SinB: Sure.
*showing off*
SinB: This is a dance called "MANIAC" that's trending these days.
SinB: If I become the class president,
SinB: I'll teach you guys.
Umji: My hidden dance instincts are awakening.
SinB: I want our class to be
SinB: the most active class in the whole school.
SinB: Please give me applause, I'm done now.
*charisma*
SinB: Thank you.
Eunha: It's been over ten years since I've last done a class president election.
Eunha: I mean, the last time was during elementary school.
SinB: Oh, but I have a question.
SinB: Is that your natural hair color?
Eunbi's unusually bright hair.
(a question shaking the foundations)
SinB: Are you mixed race?
Eunha: Yes, I am.
Umji: Where are you from?
Eunha: Let me introduce myself.
Eunha: I'll announce my promises.
Eunha: Hi, I'm Jung Eun Bi.
Eunha: The promises I have prepared are
//////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////
Eunha: Recently, I've been running a burger truck game called "My Little Chef."
Eunha: If I become the class president,
Eunha: I want to go eat burgers together.
SinB: How many times?
Eunbi finds it too difficult...
SinB: Surely it's not just once? / Eunha: How many times should we go?
Eunha: I'm still just a student...
Umji: What if I can't eat flour?
SinB: Oh, really?
SinB: Oh no.
The entire universe is against Jung Eun Bi becoming class president.
Eunha: How about going to Lotteria to eat a rice burger?
Umji: Oh, that sounds like a good idea.
Eunha: Sure.
quora: Q. Is there a place selling the discontinued Lotteria rice burger? A. No.
Eunha: Then, please take care of me, everyone.
SinB: The votes are going to be split clearly, I think?
Teacher: Everyone close your eyes.
Teacher: If you open your eyes, I will see you.
Teacher: Raise your hand if you want Yewon to be the class president.
Election assurance
Teacher: Raise your hand if you want Hwang Eun-bi to be the class president, and if you want to dance.
Hwang Eun-bi
And
The top student in school who needs an excuse to dance
Hwang Eun-bi, two votes
Teacher: Lastly, our Jung Eun-bi
Teacher: Got it.
Teacher: Shall we all open our eyes?
Excitedly
Teacher: Yewon
Teacher: became the class president.
SinB: No way
Eunha: Video review, video review!
Eunha: This isn't right, we need a video review!
Eunbi's group can't accept the election result
Teacher: Let's check the results when we get home.
Eunha: Hey, this...
Eunha: Hey, no way, the teacher picked!
Eunha: The teacher picked it!
Eunha: Was it you?
SinB: Wait a moment
SinB: Wait a moment. Time out.
SinB: Time out.
SinB: Wait a moment.
SinB: Ah, wait a moment. Time out.
But really... who are you talking to?
Umji: I didn't know you were all so studious without showing it.
Eun-bi's group still can't comprehend the result
Umji: Actually, as it's a crucial time...
SinB: What do you mean what time?
Umji: To know how studious we are.
Umji: It was a pledge to test the waters a bit.
Umji: If I really become class president,
Umji: I'll ensure a good academic atmosphere
Umji: As well as the dance time that Hwang Eun-bi loves.
Umji: And Jung Eun-bi's
Umji: time to eat hamburgers.
Umji: I think this is what a class president should do.
The class president is the best
Thank you
Shin Song Middle School Sistar~!
Eunha: Since I'm the class president for a moment,
Eunha: please give us a congratulatory performance.
SinB: It's you, right?
SinB: The one with 10 million views.
Umji: Please take care of me.
Please take care of me.
Umji: Let's get along well, Class 2-5 friends.
Teacher: Yewon will energetically lead the class.
Teacher: We will start the first period after a 10-minute break.
Teacher: Let's have the class president erase the board.
Shall we get ready for the first lesson of the new semester?
SinB: Wait a moment
SinB: I just think the voting was wrong.
SinB: This can't be happening.
SinB: Because I thought it would be me.
Eunha: Are you doing an interview now?
Appealing unfairness to the fourth wall
SinB: I thought it would be me.
First Period: Morality Class
Eunha: Excited for the first class
Teacher: Okay, for the first period
Teacher: it’s morality class
Teacher: I'll give you a topic
Teacher: and we'll split into teams to have a discussion based on that topic
Teacher: Now, the first topic
Teacher: If you could only live in
Teacher: one season for the rest of your life,
Teacher: which season would you choose?
Teacher: Let’s start by making a choice.
SinB: Winter.
Teacher: Winter.
Eunbi: It's so hard to choose.
Umji: It's autumn.
SinB: Actually, I also like autumn the best.
Eunha: I like spring too.
Umji: But we have to pick between summer and winter.
Umji: I choose summer.
SinB: Summer.
Umji: Yeah.
I'll choose summer too.
Umji: Oh, it's a summer team here.
Eunha: I choose summer too.
SinB: Winter?
SinB: Summer?
SinB: It's clear-cut.
Teams split neatly as they were seated.
Teacher: Here is summer.
Teacher: Here is winter.
Eunha: Let's start the discussion.
Umji: First of all,
Umji: I have something to say.
Umji: You guys who ran for class president earlier,
Umji: I heard your birthday is around summer.
SinB: I wanted to be born in winter.
Umji: Oh, really?
Umji: Actually, I wanted to be born in autumn, too.
SinB: I had no choice but to come out in summer.
Umji: The reason I consider it important is
Umji: Is because of the fruits.
Total agreement
Umji: There are so many delicious fruits.
Umji: Especially watermelon.
Umji: Is there anyone here who can't eat watermelon?
SinB: I can't eat it because there isn't any.
Take a bite of watermelon, SWEET
Umji: Can't give up watermelon.
Eunha: Just like someone whose main diet is fruits.
Umji: Right, my family runs a fruit farm.
Eunha: Really? Your family owns a fruit farm?
Umji: The crops need to grow well.
Umji: It gets a bit tough in the winter.
Successfully voiced her opinion and promoted the family business.
SinB: The reason it's winter
SinB: is that you can layer up in winter.
SinB: But in summer, you can't just take everything off.
SinB: Besides, it's too humid, and our country is quite hot and humid.
SinB: Summer feels sticky, but winter is dry, yet comfortable.
Umji: I thought you really hated dry weather?
SinB: No, it's not like that. Dry weather doesn't affect me as much.
SinB: I don't crack like you do.
Umji: Well, I do have dry skin, Yewon.
SinB: You're 'Dry Skin Kim Yewon,' but I'm less of a 'Dry Skin Hwang Eunbi.'
Umji: Here we're talking about comfort,
Umji: comparing winter heaters to summer air conditioners.
Umji: Doesn't summer air conditioning make you feel a lot better and refreshed?
SinB: But I'm talking about going outside.
Umji: I know you as someone who prefers indoor activities.
SinB: Of course.
SinB: Why do you think I don't go out in summer?
SinB: It's because it's hot, humid, and sticky.
Umji: I thought you don't go out in winter either.
SinB: No, I go out a lot in winter.
SinB: I go out a lot in winter.
SinB: And there's more food to eat in winter.
Umji: What are you talking about?
SinB: Fish-shaped buns (Bungeoppang).
Eunha: There's more food in summer!
SinB: What? Other than watermelon, what is there?
Eunha: No!
SinB: Just watermelon, right?
Eunha: Samgyetang (ginseng chicken soup).
Eunha: Fighting heat with heat (Iyeolchiyeol).
SinB: Oh, it's hot, it's hot.
SinB: It'll cook you.
Umji: You like naengmyeon (cold noodles) too.
SinB: Naengmyeon?
SinB: Yeah, cold with cold (Inaengchinaeng).
SinB: I eat it in winter too.
Eunha: Fighting heat with heat.
SinB: I said I eat it in winter.
Umji: Fighting heat with heat.
Eunha: I'll just speak based on my standards.
Eunha: My cheeks hurt when the wind hits them.
An unexpectedly cute reason
Eunha: They hurt and turn red.
Umji: That's quite unfortunate.
SinB: I have another definite reason.
SinB: I...
SinB: I look prettier in winter.
Eunha: I'll speak based on my standards.
Eunha: I tend to look a bit prettier in summer.
SinB: But your pores open up in summer.
Eunha: Oh!
Umji: My pores are very...
Umji: small, so I'm fine.
Eunha: Oh!
Umji: This disagreement is still quite tense.
Umji: How about you guys?
Umji: Do you look prettier in summer, or in winter?
I tend to look prettier in winter.
Umji: You do give off a winter concept vibe.
SinB: Do you know why?
SinB: Your pores tighten in winter.
Perfect logic
Indeed, it was winter...
SinB: Your pores tighten in winter,
Eunha: They become elastic.
SinB: Yeah, they become more elastic.
Umji: You're selling me on this.
SinB: Right, isn't it?
Eunha: But honestly, I do like winter more.
Umji: Actually, I think I like winter more too.
Eunha: It's not that...
SinB: Guys, clap your hands.
Eunha: No, no.
Eunha: Listen to me.
Eunha: Think about this:
Eunha: No bugs...
SinB: It's clean...
Eunha: You can wear pajamas...
SinB: Teach, please wrap this up.
SinB: I think we won.
Teacher: So the conclusion is, there's more to eat in winter,
SinB: Adding 100 points to the beauty score
Teacher: So then...
Final Verdict: If you had to live in one season: Winter
Victory for less dry Hwang Eunbi!
Teacher: Now, for the second topic.
Teacher: Is knowledge power? Or is ignorance a remedy(bliss)?
SinB: This one's really tough.
Umji: I think knowledge is power...
Umji: ...is what I believe.
SinB: Same, power.
Eunha: Then I think ignorance
Eunha: is a remedy(bliss).
But then,
This person suddenly started acting suspiciously / Eunha: Honestly, I don't have much to say.
Why is Hwang Eunbi rummaging through the desk? / Eunha: Ignorance is a remedy and also a strength...
Actually, there was a hidden mission during today's ethics class.
Find the lunch note! / Looks delicious!
During the debate, they had to find the hidden  without the teacher or friends noticing!
I wonder what kind of substitute lunch will come out if they find the note?
Teacher: Since we've changed seats,
Teacher: how about we try to persuade each other?
SinB: Class president!
SinB: Go!
Umji: I think knowledge is power.
Umji: First, a person has to face the truth
Umji: to properly deal with reality
Umji: without misunderstandings...
Eunha: Keep going?
Umji: OK.
SinB: Hey, keep going.
Umji: Thinking of keep going,
Umji: one might think 'Ignorance is a remedy' but / Hwang Eunbi is more focused on
Umji: that's a bit... / openly looking for notes...
Umji: how should I put it?
Umji: It's a kind of avoidance... / Yewon enthusiastically debates for Eunbi
SinB: I thought so too. / enthusiastically agreeing
Umji: Right?
Umji: What do you guys think?
Eunha: If you don't know...
Eunha: you don't know that you don't know, right?
Eunha: If you don't know, you won't know that you don't know.
Eunha: And actually, I'm more focused not on knowing or not knowing
Eunha: but on power and medicine.
Eunha: but I've focused on 'power' and 'medicine'.
Umji: Oh, that's different...
Eunha: I focused on 'power' and 'medicine',
Eunha: What good is power anyway?
Eunha: It only leads to fighting.
Eunha: But medicine heals people,
Eunha: wraps them in love,
Eunha: that's why I think medicine is more important,
Eunha: and medicine triumphs over power.
SinB: But I...
SinB: Whatever it is, if you don't know, you can't defend yourself when attacked,
SinB: so if you stay ignorant, you'll just keep being attacked.
SinB: You need to know at least a bit to defend yourself.
SinB: Would you rather remain ignorant and be attacked,
SinB: or be informed and defend yourself?
SinB: Try to rebuttal that.
Eunha: Well...
Eunha: there are also uncomfortable truths
Eunha: that you wish you didn't know.
Umji: Too many of them.
Umji: The world is full of Pandora's boxes.
Eunha: Once you're aware of them, they keep bothering you,
Eunha: like if you keep thinking about swallowing
Eunha: and become conscious of every time you swallow,
Eunha: from that moment...
SinB: Ah!
SinB: Why did you mention that?!
A perfect example causing distress
Eunha: See? It happens like that.
An endless debate! What will the outcome be?
SinB: What are you even talking about now?
SinB: You're talking about 'Ignorance is bliss.'
Eunha: I want to stay ignorant.
Umji: Great singer.