Jun-bin: I'm planning to do some promotions for "Devil's Plan,"
Jun-bin: or perhaps take part in other projects,
Jun-bin: and I'm thinking of filming a few domestic travels.
Ye-in: Domestic travel?
Ye-in: That sounds good. At least we can go on domestic trips,
Ye-in: relatively easily.
Jun-bin: I'll take a break from overseas travel
Jun-bin: and probably go out around November.
Ye-in: November?
Jun-bin: Can you hear me?
Production Team: Yes.
Ye-in: Because it's radio,
Jun-bin: I feel reassured just by looking at KakaoPot
Ye-in: Why?
Jun-bin: I've been doing this for so long,
Jun-bin: it feels like I'm talking with friends.
Jun-bin: I'm probably more familiar to the audience than those watching BaeTen.
Ye-in: I see.
Jun-bin: They thought Bae Seong-jae was back,
Jun-bin: what a compliment.
Jun-bin: These days, he's lost so much weight,
Ye-in: Right, he's half the man he used to be, literally.
Production Team: Looks unimpressive.
Ye-in: He looks a bit older.
Production Team: He's not here to hear this.
Jun-bin: I'm so jealous though.
Production Team: Bae Seong-jae isn't here.
Ye-in: Honestly, Bae Seong-jae oppa has always been more about pleasing the ears than the eyes.
Jun-bin: Oh, he's not here, wow.
Production Team: Exactly.
Ye-in: They're asking if we know each other well,
Ye-in: but we're actually meeting for the first time today.
Ye-in: Yes, yes.
Ye-in: It's our first encounter.
Jun-bin: Right, I just feel a bit of inner closeness.
Ye-in: I feel a strong inner closeness too.
Jun-bin: That's how nonexistent it is, for you to say that.
Ye-in: Because I've seen all of it.
Jun-bin: What did you see?
Ye-in: I watched "Wheel Mouth" and
Ye-in: then there's the "JB(loser)" stuff you did.
Jun-bin: Didn't you watch my YouTube channel?
dfd
Ye-in: I did watch some of your acting there.
Jun-bin: Really?
Ye-in: But it was all ads.
Jun-bin: You only see the parts where I appear unfavorably.
Ye-in: That's not the case.
Jun-bin: Whenever I meet someone on the street who knows "GwakTube," I greet them warmly,
Jun-bin: but if they know "Wheel Mouth," my facial expression changes a bit.
Ye-in: Why? I find the character there really fun and genuinely entertaining.
Jun-bin: You see me as a "JB," which is why I always say as an annual event,
Jun-bin: "That's all an act. Do you think I would sit there without getting paid?"
Jun-bin: That's what I say.
Ye-in: But I think in front of true love,
Ye-in: doesn't everyone become a "JB"? Isn't that right?
Ye-in: You become humble and want to do everything for the person you truly love, showing all those "JB" qualities.
Jun-bin: Oh, you're so warm-hearted.
Ye-in: Because that's how it is. You only act selfishly towards someone you don't like,
Ye-in: but in front of someone you really like, you become smaller, wanting to do well by them, showing all aspects of being a "JB."
Jun-bin: It feels like we're already doing the "Non-Romantic Champions League." We haven't even started yet.
Jun-bin: But really, the chat content and the way of speaking feel so familiar,
Jun-bin: like I'm back in my hometown, and it's very comforting.
Jun-bin: Lately, I've only seen polished comments, so this feels warm.
Ye-in: Are YouTube comments more refined?
Jun-bin: As the channel grows,
Jun-bin: more people tend to respond warmly rather than critically,
Jun-bin: so I've seen a lot of refined comments,
Jun-bin: but here, the podcast listeners
Jun-bin: still treat me as the highest "podcast veteran." To me, they're all newcomers.
Ye-in: Newcomers? Like a new Dobby?
Ye-in: Right? Right?
Jun-bin: What do you usually do for fun at home?
Ye-in: I enjoy watching movies, and if I had enough money and time, I'd travel just like you.
Ye-in: Earlier this year, I didn't have money but had plenty of time, so I traveled a bit.
Jun-bin: Really?
Ye-in: I even went to Hawaii.
Jun-bin: Because you had money and time?
Ye-in: No money, but plenty of time.
Jun-bin: Then you can't go to Hawaii?
Ye-in: I went to Hawaii at that time.
Jun-bin: But Hawaii is expensive.
Ye-in: But I went, and it really was expensive. Every meal there was costly.
Jun-bin: I was shocked by the prices in Hawaii, especially because of the tips.
Jun-bin: With tips included, even simple meals can cost around 20-30,000 won.
Ye-in: Even a sandwich, just a basic one with some salmon, costs about 20-30,000 won.
Jun-bin: So, a sandwich is 20,000 won, and a meal can be 30,000 to 40,000 won.
Ye-in: Right, I also went to Osaka.
Ye-in: Just yesterday, there were three of us, all noisy,
Jun-bin: Who was on yesterday?
Ye-in: Yesterday, our members were on.
Jun-bin: Which members came?
Ye-in: Ji-ae unnie and Su-jeong unnie.
Jun-bin: Oh.
Ye-in: Who do you like the most in Lovelyz?
Jun-bin: I like Ye-in the most.
00:04:
Ye-in: Correct.
Ye-in: [Everyone in the radio studio laughs.]
Production Team: Why do both of you sound like robots?
Jun-bin: I'm a bit nervous,
Jun-bin: because I'm a fan of Lovelyz.
Production Team: We have some acting coming up.
Production Team: Both of you.
Jun-bin: If we're going to act,
Ye-in: It's a love scene, right?
Ye-in: Mr. GwakTube,
Jun-bin: I don't think I can do it.
Jun-bin: Maybe it's better if you do it alone.
Ye-in: No way.
Ye-in: Jun-bin oppa, can I start?
Ye-in: That's the first thing.
Jun-bin: It's tough.
Ye-in: Oppa,
Jun-bin: This is harder than 'Devil's Plan.'
Production Team: There's a part where you make a fart sound.
Jun-bin: Got it.
Production Team: Mr. GwakTube,
Jun-bin: Normally, people who draw lines say Mr. GwakTube.
Jun-bin: Right?
Ye-in: Because,
Ye-in: If I suddenly call you oppa since we just met,
Ye-in: It might be burdensome.
Production Team: There's also this,
Ye-in: Ah, Mr. Jun-bin, Mr. Jun-bin,
Ye-in: Somehow, Mr. Jun-bin feels a bit distant.
Jun-bin: No, I like being called by my name.
Ye-in: Then, Jun-bin?
Ye-in: [Everyone laughs]
Ye-in: I'll call you Jun-bin oppa.
Production Team: It's competitive.
Ye-in: Can I call you oppa?
Ye-in: During the broadcast,
Production Team: On the broadcast,
Ye-in: Mr. Jun-bin,
Production Team: Yes, yes.
Ye-in: Okay, got it.
Jun-bin: This broadcast is a bit strange.
Jun-bin: No, it's not.
Production Team: But, like now,
Production Team: When it's not included, you can call him oppa.
Ye-in: Since it's only my second time as a DJ,
Ye-in: I might stutter a bit, but I'll do my best.
Jun-bin: I haven't done much radio either,
Jun-bin: so it feels awkward.
Ye-in: You've done much tougher things than radio.
Jun-bin: That may be true, but radio is just
Jun-bin: my voice going out, so it's okay, but also nerve-wracking because it's live.
Jun-bin: I used to do live broadcasts a lot in the past,
Jun-bin: but I've reduced them lately.
Jun-bin: Afraid of making a mistake?
Ye-in: Yes, yes.
Jun-bin: Yes.
Ye-in: Right, you have something to maintain.
Ye-in: That's why I rarely do live broadcasts.
Jun-bin: I used to do live twice a week.
Ye-in: Really?
Jun-bin: Yes, I loved doing live.
Jun-bin: Lately, I've been watching mostly streaming stuff,
Jun-bin: like game streaming.
Jun-bin: I'm actually pretty good with live,
Jun-bin: but I've been more cautious lately.
Production Team: Alright, let's start with the opening.
Production Team: This Sunday, October 8th, opening.
Ye-in: 'Breaking news'
Ye-in: 'GwakTube'
Ye-in: 'A swimming hopeful inspired by the Hangzhou Asian Games'
Ye-in: 'A man who becomes a hot topic no matter what he does'
Ye-in: Hello, it's Sunday, October 8th, 2023.
Ye-in: Filling in for DJ Bae Seong-jae, who's away for the Asian Games broadcast,
Ye-in: I'm Special DJ Jung Ye-in, bringing you Jung Ye-in's Ten.
Ye-in: The first song was Oh My Girl's 'Dolphin.'
10 o'clock headlines: GwakTube, a swimming hopeful inspired by the Hangzhou Asian Games
00:07
Ye-in: A man who becomes a hot topic no matter what he does.
Ye-in: GwakTube posted a picture at the pool on Instagram, and it immediately became news.
Ye-in: Seeing news made from SNS, he really seems to be a hot topic.
Ye-in: Here's the photo attached,
Ye-in: looking cute in a red hat, but the water looks shallow.
Ye-in: Watching the video he posted,
Ye-in: he was learning basic moves with a kickboard.
Ye-in: If you're going to swim, you should learn diligently,
Ye-in: like Mr. GwakTube.
Ye-in: Like him,
Ye-in: those inspired by the Asian Games to register for swimming,
Ye-in: badminton, and table tennis,
Ye-in: are numerous.
Ye-in: Please don't just burn out during the Asian Games period,
Ye-in: and continue to exercise healthily for a long time.
Ye-in: Got it, Mr. GwakTube?
Jun-bin: Yes, I'll be careful.
Ye-in: Non-Romantic Champions League
Ye-in: Let's do it again.
Ye-in: In the Non-Romantic Champions League corner,
Ye-in: it's hard to tease singles since I'm in the same boat,
Ye-in: so instead of non-romance,
Ye-in: let's slightly change to a miserable corner for bad manners.
Ye-in: We'll go with the Bad Manners Champions League.
Ye-in: And we have a very special
Ye-in: guest with us,
Ye-in: a man who fits well with BaeTen,
Ye-in: travel YouTuber GwakTube.
Ye-in: So, together with him,
Ye-in: we'll judge the bad manner stories of those who cross the line.
Ye-in: This is Jung Ye-in's Ten.
Ye-in: You can watch the entire recording process of YengTen,
Ye-in: and participate in the chat by entering the original DJ BaeDi's name, Bae Seong-jae, in KakaoTV,
Ye-in: or by visiting the Erao channel on YouTube.
Ye-in: You can also join the chat there,
Ye-in: so feel free to come in and play with us.
Ye-in: Now, let's introduce the gifts.
Ye-in: Then, we'll be back after the commercials.
Production Team: We'll start the corner now.
Ye-in: Jun-bin-kun, if you don't know Lovelyz's songs in front of Lovelyz,
Ye-in: that's bad manners, you know.
Ye-in: Do you know any Lovelyz songs?
Jun-bin: I'd love to sing many, but my favorite is definitely 'Ah-Choo.'
Jun-bin: You have to sing a verse to move on.
Jun-bin: 'I want to make something delicious for you'
Ye-in: I'm gonna die of hunger.
Jun-bin: Yes.
Ye-in: Ah, that's 'Ah-Choo.' Thank you.
Ye-in: Aww.
Jun-bin: Thank you.
Ye-in: You pass.
Ye-in: You're acknowledged as a manner man.
Ye-in: Since I've subscribed to GwakTube as well,
Ye-in: do you acknowledge me as a manner girl?
Jun-bin: Oh, absolutely, I acknowledge you.
Ye-in: Ah, thank you.
Jun-bin: It's acknowledging each other as manner man
Jun-bin: GwakTube and manner girl
Jun-bin: YengDi, and
Jun-bin: we'll precisely pick out
Jun-bin: the annoyingly bad-mannered people around us
Jun-bin: and criticize them.
Ye-in: Miserable Special Bad Manners
Jun-bin: Champions League
Ye-in: Oh, the BG gets grand.
Ye-in: Today's Bad Manners Champions League, joining us today is
Ye-in: a vibrant travel creator
Ye-in: a friend of singles
Ye-in: surpassing the hope of bashful BaeTen enthusiasts,
Ye-in: now a celebrity among celebrities,
Ye-in: a celeb among celebs.
Ye-in: And having appeared on the brain game survival show,
Ye-in: demonstrating his intelligence as well,
Ye-in: the most trending broadcaster nowadays,
Ye-in: GwakTube, Gwak Jun-bin, welcome.
Jun-bin: Hello, I'm Gwak Jun-bin, a travel creator
Jun-bin: and currently appearing on "Devil's Plan."
Jun-bin: Nice to meet you.
Jun-bin: Glad to be here.
Ye-in: Wow, a celebrity.
Ye-in: You visited BaeTen last October,
returning after a year not to BaeTen but
Ye-in: to YengTen. Welcome back.
Jun-bin: I'm really glad to be back.
Ye-in: And you're a fan of Lovelyz,
Ye-in: so it's really nice that you mentioned that right away,
Ye-in: making me feel very good.
Ye-in: But in fact, we're meeting for the first time, right?
Jun-bin: Yes, this is our first meeting.
Ye-in: But we feel a kind of inner closeness, don't we?
Jun-bin: Absolutely, I feel a huge closeness.
Ye-in: I also feel a strong inner closeness.
Ye-in: "Ah-Choo" is your favorite among our songs,
Ye-in: and what other song do you like?
Jun-bin: So, we're starting the Bad Manners Champions League, but
Jun-bin: I actually know a lot, but I can't remember right now.
Ye-in: You're preparing to stretch your tongue, right?
Ye-in: To make it longer.
Jun-bin: No, really,
I know, but I can't remember right now.
Jun-bin: You suddenly asked me.
Ye-in: How many members are in Lovelyz?
Jun-bin: I can even tell you all the members' names of Lovelyz.
Ye-in: Really?
Jun-bin: Yes.
Ye-in: My name is
Jun-bin: Jung Ye-in.
Ye-in: Right, right.
Ye-in: Who's your favorite member?
Jun-bin: Jung Ye-in.
Ye-in: That's right, that's right.
Jun-bin: I can talk about all the other members too.
Ye-in: Thank you so much.
Ye-in: When you heard Jun-bin was coming,
Ye-in: comments like this came up.
Ye-in: Hong Tae-young said,
Ye-in: 'This combination... (what does it mean?)'
Ye-in: like this.
Jun-bin: That's something I use a lot
Jun-bin: in my channel content.
Ye-in: Yes!
Jun-bin: When I'm sort of flirting with girls,
Jun-bin: and nobody thinks it's anything,
Jun-bin: but I pretend it's something by saying, 'What does it mean?'
Jun-bin: I hope you don't misunderstand too much.
Jun-bin: I didn't want to start off too burdensome.
Jun-bin: But you're kind of a person who causes a lot of misunderstandings.
Ye-in: Yes, because, well, when we travel, I don't know who I'll go with,
Ye-in: but sure, we can go together.
Jun-bin: Not at all.
Jun-bin: I don't even contact female friends.
Ye-in: Right, it's either dating or strangers.
Jun-bin: Yes, exactly.
Jun-bin: I do have female colleagues, though.
Ye-in: So, can we be work colleagues then?
Jun-bin: Starting off by drawing lines like this...
Ye-in: [Everyone laughs]
Ye-in: No, no, because I don't want to be a stranger, so
Jun-bin: Yes, yes, yes.
Ye-in: we can play board games and spend time together like that, right?
Jun-bin: Often?
Ye-in: Like, we can get together often.
Jun-bin: Should I use 'What does it mean?' now?
Ye-in: Oh! The word 'often'!
Ye-in: I'm being very careful with my words today.
Jun-bin: You should be careful with me too.
Ye-in: Yes, yes.
Ye-in: I usually like to talk like this,
Ye-in: but every time you say 'What does it mean?' just tell me directly.
Ye-in: I'll try to be more careful.
Jun-bin: That's a thought I keep to myself,
Jun-bin: so I think the phrase 'What does it mean?' has its own charm.
Ye-in: Ah.
Ye-in: Also, Olbyu commented, 'So envious of PaniBottle who's close with BLACKPINK's Jisoo and GwakTube who meets Lovelyz's Ye-in... what are you guys?'
Ye-in: What do you think?
Jun-bin: Well, I think the latter might be true,
Jun-bin: but I'll try my best to make it funny.
Ye-in: Sure, I think we'll get along really well.
Jun-bin: That's why I'm nervous now.
Ye-in: What does it mean?
Ye-in: Are you asking me what it means now?
Jun-bin: Yes, yes, yes.
Jun-bin: I'm getting nervous now,
Jun-bin: I did a radio show last week too,
Jun-bin: I was on Cultwo Show last week, and it was
Jun-bin: my second appearance on SBS, but
Jun-bin: this feels three times more nerve-wracking.
Ye-in: Really?
Ye-in: You'll get used to it soon and your nerves will melt away.
Ye-in: Also, Kuku1204 commented, 'PaniBottle is close with BLACKPINK's Jisoo and GwakTube meets Lovelyz's Ye-in... you guys are so lucky.. what are you?'
Ye-in: Like this.
Jun-bin: It's Lovelyz's Jisoo, but
Ye-in: Yeah, Jisoo unnie and I are really close too,
Jun-bin: I don't know BLACKPINK's Jisoo at all,
Ye-in: You don't know each other?
Jun-bin: Not at all,
Ye-in: Really?
Ye-in: Right.
Ye-in: I thought you liked the name Jisoo.
Jun-bin: Not at all,
Jun-bin: I played board games with Jisoo at PaniBottle's house once.
Ye-in: See, without me,
Jun-bin: How could I know
Ye-in: Contact Jisoo unnie, then
Ye-in: let's do it together next time.
Jun-bin: Do we really need to go through her?
Ye-in: What does it mean?
Jun-bin: You can't just use that randomly.
Jun-bin: I was serious... never mind.
Ye-in: Alright, I understand.
Ye-in: How was it meeting Jisoo unnie?
Jun-bin: She was really fun and cheerful, right?
Ye-in: Yes.
Jun-bin: Her personality seems very similar to yours.
Ye-in: Yes, Lovelyz,
Ye-in: though our group name is Lovelyz,
Ye-in: we're actually like bold warriors in personality,
Ye-in: so we're very straightforward.
Jun-bin: She was quite bold.
Ye-in: Yes, next time I want to join too.
Ye-in: Jun-bin, these days you're so popular that there's hardly anyone who doesn't know you.
Ye-in: Do you actually feel the popularity?
Ye-in: Are you aware of your popularity?
Jun-bin: Rather than popularity, I guess I'm starting to really feel the recognition.
Jun-bin: For example, even today, after swimming,
Jun-bin: the ladies at the pool recognized me and kept greeting me.
Jun-bin: They knew me even at the swimming pool.
Ye-in: Wow, even the ladies there?
Jun-bin: Yes, yes.
Jun-bin: But it's the first time someone said to me
Jun-bin: that I look better on broadcast than in person.
Ye-in: Oh, better on screen than in person.
Ye-in: But that's actually a compliment.
Ye-in: Because, ultimately, more people see us on TV, like a hundred or two hundred times more.
Ye-in: Looking better on TV isn't easy, you know.
Ye-in: It's hard to look better on TV.
Ye-in: Than in person.
Jun-bin: So I was a bit embarrassed then.
Ye-in: No, but seeing you in person,
Ye-in: it's definitely not like that.
Ye-in: You look just the same as on TV.
Jun-bin: That's the comment I hear the most.
Jun-bin: That I look the same.
Ye-in: Exactly, yes.
Ye-in: How can someone be so consistent? I hear that a lot.
Ye-in: What about me?
Ye-in: Between TV and real life, which looks better?
Jun-bin: In real life, you're much more beautiful.
Ye-in: Thank you.
Ye-in: How satisfied are you with your life these days?
Jun-bin: Well, I'm happiest when doing broadcasts like this, satisfied,
Jun-bin: seeing and talking to people I've been a fan of,
Jun-bin:
face to face.
Jun-bin: Every time I'm on such shows, my happiness increases.
Ye-in: Since you'll continue to be active in broadcasting,
Ye-in: I guess you'll be on shows with even more beautiful celebrities, right?
Jun-bin: I think being friendly with celebrities is more important to me,
Jun-bin: the ones I like.
Ye-in: Don't forget me then, okay?
Jun-bin: Yes, yes, I'll keep coming back.
Ye-in: And you're a travel YouTuber, right?
Ye-in: You're always traveling, where have you been recently?
Jun-bin: Recently, I went on a trip to Central America,
Jun-bin: the last destination was Cuba, with Noh Hong-chul and PaniBottle.
Ye-in: Wow, how was it?
Jun-bin: In Cuba, nothing works, not even phones,
Jun-bin: well, they do but barely,
Jun-bin: it's almost better not to use them because of the stress,
Jun-bin: but everything in the country is like it stopped in the '70s and '80s,
Jun-bin: so it's worth visiting once before you die.
Ye-in: It seems like a break from the busy modern society,
Ye-in: returning to our original state.
Jun-bin: Really, there's nothing, just the pure essence, and no food either.
Ye-in: Then what do you eat to live?
Jun-bin: There's nothing tasty, nothing tasty.
Ye-in: Oh, nothing tasty.
Jun-bin: Yes, we just eat spaghetti and pizza, but
Jun-bin: the country itself has so much romance that I recommend visiting at least once.
Ye-in: Oh, at least once.
Ye-in: Someday, when I'm tired of this busy modern society,
Jun-bin: Yes, yes, I really recommend it then.
Ye-in: Can I contact you for advice then?
Ye-in: Like, for advice.
Jun-bin: Oh, I thought you were suggesting we go together.
Jun-bin: You really make a lot of assumptions.
Ye-in: Yes, because, who knows, maybe at that time, I don't know who I'll go with,
Ye-in: but sure, we can go together.
Ye-in: Can I write my story for the "Non-Romantic Champions League"?
Ye-in: I'll listen to one of your stories today and then we'll move on. Meanwhile,
Ye-in: despite being busy with traveling, you're currently appearing on the popular Tengflix reality show,
Ye-in: "Brain Game Survival Devil's Plan". Did you apply to be on it yourself?
Jun-bin: Not exactly an application, but I expressed a lot of interest. I'm a fan of the creator, PD Jong-hyun,
Jun-bin: who has made many programs I greatly admire.
Jun-bin: So, I said I wanted to be on that show, and
Jun-bin: when I was in Korea for travel, I immediately went for an interview and got selected to participate.
Ye-in: What kind of questions do they ask in the interview for such a scary game?
Jun-bin: Surprisingly, they seemed to focus a lot on understanding my personality.
Ye-in: Oh......
Jun-bin: I don't remember exactly what I said,
Ye-in: Mm......
Jun-bin: but I think I talked a lot about my feelings and thoughts on games I've seen before.
Ye-in: Do you naturally have a smart image?
Jun-bin: I neither have an image nor am I smart.
Ye-in: I haven't watched "Devil's Plan" yet, but I plan to watch it tonight before going to bed.
Jun-bin: It's a brain survival show, so people might find it hard to start because it seems difficult,
Jun-bin: but it's actually quite accessible, and although the rules explanation is a bit long,
Jun-bin: you can skip it without missing out on understanding the game.
Ye-in: Right, why is it so long? I have to reread the beginning because the explanation is too lengthy.
Ye-in: I'm a bit of a dummy.
Jun-bin: If it's not long, people might complain about the lack of explanation,
Jun-bin: so they provide it, but you can still follow the game without it, no problem.
Ye-in: Unrelated.
Jun-bin: It's a show where you
can see people's brain battles, political battles.
Ye-in: What was your role there?
Jun-bin: At first, I thought I was the main character, but after watching the broadcast,
Jun-bin: it turned out I was only the main character in interviews.
Ye-in: Who?
Jun-bin: Me. In individual interviews, I talked as if I was the main character,
Jun-bin: but in terms of gameplay, it wasn't really like that.
Ye-in: So, you played dirty?
Jun-bin: Dirty, but also comedic plays were my thing.
Ye-in: Like bluffing?
Jun-bin: Yes, exactly, I was like a comedian there.
Ye-in: Maybe that's why you were chosen? Every group needs such a presence.
Jun-bin: Like you said, in interviews, I was like 'Yagami Light' from 'Death Note',
Jun-bin: but in play, just
Ye-in: a passing pedestrian.
Jun-bin: Not quite that, but maybe one of 'Light's targets for manipulation.
Ye-in: Still high up there.
Jun-bin: I wanted to show more of my gameplay, but "Devil's Plan" isn't over yet.
Ye-in: Right, right.
Jun-bin: Not all episodes have been released yet.
Ye-in: Right, as of now, up to episode 9 has been released.
Jun-bin: Yes.
Ye-in: It says here you played the role of being smitten with yourself in episode 1, is that correct?
Jun-bin: That smugness,
Jun-bin: well, interviews and gameplay are different,
Jun-bin: during gameplay, I think I did well, really well,
Jun-bin: and in interviews, I was like, "Who should I save?" pretending to be all that.
Ye-in: As if the game was in my hands.
Jun-bin: But it turns out, everyone played that way, not just me.
Ye-in: So, it wasn't just me.
Jun-bin: And I watched the program too much, so maybe I caught that bug.
Ye-in: It was filmed early this January
, right?
Jun-bin: Yes.
Ye-in: The results are already out by now,
Ye-in: but can we expect to see more of your actions? Please promote it a bit.
Jun-bin: If you want to see my actions, just watch it.
Jun-bin: Because there's a lot of me, I hogged the camera.
Jun-bin: A lot of screentime.
Ye-in: That's the best.
Jun-bin: Seeing someone so overbearing, can he achieve a human victory?
Jun-bin: Maybe that narrative might make it interesting for you.
Ye-in: But it's like an elimination concept, right? So, does it end with a final winner?
Jun-bin: Yes, exactly. The last person takes home up to 500 million won.
5 billion?
Jun-bin: Yes.
Ye-in: Amazing.
Jun-bin: You should keep a good image with me.
Ye-in: Did you win? But if you reveal that here, won't you get taken away?
Ye-in: Like, for breaking contracts or something?
Jun-bin: More than that, the officials
Ye-in: Will they make you spit it out?
Jun-bin: I probably won't be able to show my face on Netflix again.
Ye-in: Ah.
Jun-bin: Tengflix, I mean.
Ye-in: Right, right. It's so intriguing, especially after talking to you, I'm even more curious.
Ye-in: Meeting famous people like PD Kim Tae-ho, senior Yoo Jae-suk, senior Park Jung-min, Chillman, senior Noh Hong-chul, senior Jung Hyung-don, and becoming close friends with many, who's your closest friend these days?
Jun-bin: Oh, recently,
Jun-bin: until the trip to Cuba, naturally Hong-chul and PaniBottle were my closest friends,
Jun-bin: and this week, I've been meeting players from 'Devil's Plan' like Kyung-rim, Seok-jin, Dong-jun, Gwe-do, Seung-kwan, so I've gotten quite close to them.
Jun-bin: Lately, I've been getting closer to those participants.
Ye-in: Ah, including me then.
29,000
Jun-bin: I'll go around saying Ye-in is my closest friend.
Ye-in: Yes, you must say that.
Jun-bin: I've found a friend who wants to eat delicious food.
Ye-in: Delicious food?
Ye-in: Yes, I'm not in charge of cooking, but I was the one who couldn't cook there,
Jun-bin: Ah.
Ye-in: I can't cook, but we can just pay for food, right?
Jun-bin: Right, I might have a lot of money by then.
Ye-in: Exactly.
Jun-bin: I'll buy a lot with that.
Ye-in: Right, I'm curious, even if you don't win the prize, do you get paid per episode?
Jun-bin: I'm not sure if I'm allowed to talk about that?
Ye-in: [Everyone in the radio studio laughs.]
Jun-bin: I really want to tell you because the order looks interesting,
Ye-in: Can you tell me after the broadcast is over? I'm just curious about the existence, not the amount.
Jun-bin: Yes. There's an official here, so I'll ask and let you know.
Ye-in: Oh, I'm sorry.
Ye-in: Well, that's it for now. Next time on BaeTen, please come with the 'Devil's Plan'
Ye-in: friends you're close with to BaeTen.
Jun-bin: Sure, I'll definitely come.
Ye-in: Alright, let's wrap up. Our next segment, the Bad Manners Champions League, is about
Jun-bin: I'll be there for sure.
Ye-in: Yes, so, we'll introduce texts about bad manners next.
Ye-in: If you're unsure whether you're being rude or have stories of others' bad manners, send them in,
Ye-in: and we'll empathize and harshly criticize, identifying the bad manners.
Ye-in: The featured stories will receive a 'Sunrise Portable Lantern'.
Jun-bin: Wow, that's really nice.
Ye-in: Jun-bin, are you often told you're mannerly?
Jun-bin: I'm often told I'm all manners.
Ye-in: Manners or nothing at all.
Jun-bin: Literally nothing but manners.
Ye-in: Really? But you play dirty here.
Jun-bin: Ah, it's survival, you see.
Ye-in: Work is work.
Jun-bin: I don't do such things in society.
Ye-in: Ahahaha.
Jun-bin: In society, I'm a super mannerly man.
Ye-in: What kind of manners? There are various kinds of manners, right?
Jun-bin: Mainly, I'm considerate, thinking about how to please the person.
Ye-in: Mm, how to make the person comfortable.
Jun-bin: Yes, so I'm not naturally mannerly but rather artificially mannerly.
Ye-in: But that's your charm, you know, being a bit clunky.
Ye-in: You do it because women find it cute, right?
Jun-bin: Well, in my 31 years of life,
Jun-bin: I've been called cute a lot, but
Jun-bin: I've come to feel that it's meaningless.
Ye-in: But you know, being cute is everything?
Ye-in: It's a real charm, more than being cool, beautiful, or smart.
Ye-in: Being cute is truly a significant charm.
Jun-bin: It does seem to have meaning, yeah.
Ye-in: [Everyone in the radio studio laughs.]
Ye-in: What does that mean? [laughs]
Ye-in: Hahaha.
Ye-in: So, how about me? What have you heard? Do I have manners?
Jun-bin: Have you heard that? That you're mannerly?
Ye-in: I hear I'm considerate, but people use "considerate" more for women than "mannerly".
Jun-bin: Is that so?
Ye-in: I try to make others comfortable because I like it, but I don't know how they feel.
Ye-in: Have you heard from others that you're very considerate?
Jun-bin: Have people around you said you're very considerate?
Ye-in: They say that, but later people like Ji-ae might say, "What manners do you have?" and so on.
,280
Jun-bin: So, you don't have them.
Ye-in: Yes, I can't say anything. So, how am I doing so far?
Jun-bin: Perfect.
Ye-in: Perfect?
Ye-in: Hahaha.
Ye-in: Thank you. Well, let's introduce the bad manners texts we've received.
Production Team: Please look at page 10, page 10.
Production Team: On page 10, there's a special star.
Production Team: On page 10, with a star separately.
Ye-in: Then we'll move to part two after this,
Ye-in: and we'll do this, right?
Production Team: Yes, just look at page 10 then.
Production Team: You two take turns introducing the stories,
Production Team: introduce the stories and comment on whether they're bad manners or not.
Ye-in: Mm, yes.
Jun-bin: Are we reading this?
Ye-in: Yes.......
Production Team: Start with "Let's introduce the texts" and then take turns.
Production Team: I'll give you the mic back.
Ye-in: We've received a lot of stories, but Jun-bin, could you please read the first one?
Ye-in: Yes.....
Jun-bin: This is from Mr. Lee Kyung-soo,
Jun-bin: [I went on a trip abroad with a friend.]
Jun-bin: [My friend started chatting in English with some foreigners we met there.]
Jun-bin: [I couldn't speak English, so I just stood there, doing nothing.]
Jun-bin: [Curious about their conversation, I asked what they were talking about.]
Jun-bin: [They said it was nothing much and didn't tell me.]
Jun-bin: [Is it rude of my friend to talk only in English with others and exclude me during our trip?]
Ye-in: But Jun-bin, you speak English well, don't you?
Jun-bin: I do speak English, and I also speak Russian, but this happens quite often.
Jun-bin: Looking at the situation, it feels rude to me, but honestly, I find myself in similar situations often.
Jun-bin: For example, when I travel to Russia or Russian-speaking countries, I'm the only one who can speak Russian.
Jun-bin: You can guess what's being said in English, but you can't guess in Russian.
Jun-bin: I keep getting asked.
Jun-bin: Even things I think are trivial, like when I say I'm going to the supermarket and they ask where it is and say they'll go too.
Jun-bin: How to get to the supermarket? The person would say, go this way, have a nice day.
Jun-bin: Then, my friend would ask me everything about that interaction.
Jun-bin: But I'm not a translator.
Ye-in: Right, right.
Jun-bin: It's impossible to explain every little detail.
Ye-in: Of course. Although I'm not very good at English, I can understand it enough to travel.
Ye-in: Sometimes I ask.
Ye-in: And I find it really fun to explain.
Jun-bin: Oh, because I speak English well?
Ye-in: I love explaining exactly what I heard to them, I'm the type who loves to explain everything from A to Z, maybe because I haven't traveled much?
Ye-in: I think the cases I thought of were more about work or related fields than travel.
Jun-bin: When traveling, you only use simple language, so it would have been okay to explain. Now that we talk about it.
Jun-bin: Can't you just say a few words in Russian?
Ye-in: Sure, 'Thank you.'
Jun-bin: Ah... 'Gracias'.
Ye-in: 'Gracias'?
Jun-bin: 'I love you'.
Ye-in: 'I love you'?
Jun-bin: Yes.
Jun-bin: You should ask what it means.
Ye-in: What does it mean?
Jun-bin: 'Gracias' means beautiful.
Jun-bin: 'I love you' means I love you.
Ye-in: Wow! What? Please say it again.
Ye-in: What was it?
Jun-bin: 'I love you'.
Ye-in: I love you?
Jun-bin: I love you?
Ye-in: I love you.
Jun-bin: You.
Ye-in: You?
Jun-bin: You means you.
Jun-bin: I love you.
Ye-in: I love you, too.
Jun-bin: Yes.
Jun-bin: Likewise.
Ye-in: Oh, me too, right?
Jun-bin: Yes.
Ye-in: [Everyone in the radio studio laughed.]
Ye-in: Hahahaha
Ye-in: Just... take it easy in the comments.
Jun-bin: Seems like we're being rude, aren't we?
Ye-in: They say we've caused a broadcast accident.
Jun-bin: Yes, yes.
Ye-in: Hey, who's flirting on air?
Jun-bin: Was this on air?
Ye-in: Yes.
Jun-bin: Oh, sorry.
Ye-in: Yes. The camera is rolling right now.
Jun-bin: Oh, I didn't know. I didn't know.
Ye-in: Yes, yes. I forgot for a moment too.
Jun-bin: Yes, yes, yes.
Ye-in: I love you. Yes.
Ye-in: It's fun because...
Ye-in: Being fluent in languages is a huge charm point.
Ye-in: And when you're abroad, women tend to...
Ye-in: Rely on someone like that, you know?
Ye-in: You know?
Jun-bin: Yes, yes.
Ye-in: But just like that, I love you.
Ye-in: When you do this.
Ye-in: Then, wow.
Ye-in: "Jun-bin-kun is so cool." That's how it goes.
Jun-bin: That's a good tip. Oh.
Ye-in: Yes. But then again, he didn't answer when I went.
Jun-bin: So, in the case of a conversation during a trip, it's right for me to inform,
Jun-bin: But is that friend right?
Jun-bin: Are they not on good terms?
Ye-in: Right. If you're talking with foreigners you met locally and can't join the conversation,
Ye-in: It's not just about asking directions again, but understanding the ongoing
Ye-in: conversation. If it's like this, you do feel left out.
Jun-bin: Traveling really lets you know a lot about a friend.
Ye-in: Right.
Jun-bin: It's a really good thing, I think.
Jun-bin: This, in reality, isn't about not informing,
Jun-bin: but the friend being too engrossed in talking with a foreigner and wanting to talk a lot.
Jun-bin: You see your friend every day in Korea.
Jun-bin: But abroad, they might get a bit carried away.
Jun-bin: That friend.
Ye-in: I think this is rude.
Ye-in: What do you think?
Jun-bin: It depends on the situation, not exactly rude but something that could be resolved through conversation.
Ye-in: Ah, a matter for discussion.
Jun-bin: Yes.
Ye-in: I chose it as rude, and Jun-bin-kun thinks it might be good to have a conversation as a solution.
Ye-in: It wouldn't hurt to try talking it out.
Ye-in: If you talk honestly, the friend might say, "Oh, I didn't realize."
Ye-in: And then they might be more considerate.
Ye-in: Yes. That's right.
Jun-bin: Yes, that's correct.
Ye-in: Yes. Let's move on to the next story.
Ye-in: From Ppoglee.
Ye-in: [I've never been in a relationship.]
Ye-in: [I complained to my female friend, wondering why I can't get a girlfriend.]
Ye-in: [She said there are people who like your style.]
Ye-in: [And that people like you become popular as they age.]
Ye-in: [I'm in my mid-30s.]
Ye-in: [Is she telling me to stay single until my 40s?]
Ye-in: [And is it rude of my female friend to say this without intending to date me?]
Ye-in: Either give me hope or don't.
Jun-bin: Totally rude. This person is.
Ye-in: Ah, this one is definitely rude.
Jun-bin: The worst manners on Earth.
Ye-in: Ah, the worst manners on Earth.
Jun-bin: Yes, yes, yes.
Ye-in: Which part exactly?
Jun-bin: Saying people like you are popular and then not dating.
Jun-bin: It's like giving hope. This person is.
Jun-bin: So giving hope like that is rude.
Jun-bin: You can say such things.
Jun-bin: In fact, this friend Ppoglee likes the person who said this. In reality.
Jun-bin: This female friend.
Ye-in: Ah, Ppoglee likes this female friend.
Jun-bin: Likes her, so "Why can't I get a girlfriend?" is like a confession. This is.
Ye-in: Wow, I never imagined that subtext.
Jun-bin: These shy people often think they're good at confessing. There are many memes about confession attacks.
Jun-bin: They think they're good at confessing, but.
Ye-in: Confession villain.
Jun-bin: They're really not good at confessing. The real villains are just 1%, and.
Jun-bin: Most people like me can't really confess and just probe around.
Jun-bin: "This conversation came up. Let's fit in here."
Jun-bin: What does it mean? They text friends asking, "She said this, what does it mean?" "What does this mean?"
Jun-bin: Then the friend would say, "Hey, what are you confessing for?"
Jun-bin: "That's practically saying let's date." That's what friends say.
Jun-bin: Then you go confess, get rejected, and come back.
Ye-in: But I want to give a somewhat boring consolation.
Ye-in: Normally, two people liking each other's actions is hard not because it's Jun-bin or anyone else,
Ye-in: but because it's inherently difficult.
Ye-in: If it was easy, we'd all be happily married and dating
Ye-in: and living in love. But that's not the case, right?
Ye-in: Because everyone has their tastes, finding someone who matches perfectly is inherently difficult.
Ye-in: And in cases like this, it's the same. One side might like it, the other might not.
Ye-in: But think about it. Any answer to such a question feels bad.
Ye-in: "Why can't I get a girlfriend?" It's a negative question.
Ye-in: Even if you give a positive answer, it's hard to feel good about it.
Ye-in: How curious must a mid-30s single person be?
Ye-in: "Why is it like this? What's wrong with my life? I just want to experience dating, even holding hands."
Ye-in: Wasn't it a desperate question for this friend?
Ye-in: Oh, it could have been. Really wondering.
Jun-bin: How heartbroken. I'm not single, though.
Ye-in: So, you're not single, right?
Jun-bin: Yes, that's right.
Ye-in: You've been dating for a long time, even. Your girlfriend.
Jun-bin: You know well? Why do you know so well? Anyway.
Ye-in: [Everyone laughed in the radio studio.]
Ye-in: Hahahahaha
Jun-bin: This person is so desperate
Jun-bin: Of course, in a normal situation, saying such things is neither rude nor polite, but just consoling.
Jun-bin: But given how desperate this person's situation seems, it feels a bit like giving false hope.
Ye-in: Okay. Got it. So, not just some lame consolation, but actually, "Please get married." Like suggesting blind dates.
Jun-bin: You should just give them a reality check. Actually.
Ye-in: Oh, really?
Jun-bin: Yes. Yes. Yes.
Ye-in: What if they get hurt?
Jun-bin: That can't be helped.
Ye-in: So, just tell them the reality?
Jun-bin: You have to tell them the reality. You can't just let them fantasize. You have to let them know the reality.
Ye-in: Why? Just go home and look in the mirror.
Ye-in: [Everyone laughed in the radio studio.]
Jun-bin: Are you talking about personality?
Ye-in: No, I mean, you can see personality in the mirror. Personality shows on your face, you know.
Jun-bin: Oh, I see.
Ye-in: Yes. So, for example, if you're often angry, your eyebrows look angry, and if you don't brush your teeth well, your teeth are yellow. Your lifestyle and inner personality show on your face.
Jun-bin: So, you're saying to groom your eyebrows.
Ye-in: Yes. Yes. That's what I meant. I was talking about looking into the mirror of your heart.
Jun-bin: Ah, as expected. Ye-in is amazing.
Ye-in: Yep. The mirror of the heart. It's not about a one-dimensional mirror.
Jun-bin: Your insight is tremendous.
Ye-in: Yes. Yes. Yes.
Ye-in: In fact, what's most important is what's inside us.
Jun-bin: Yes. Yes. Yes.
Ye-in: Yes. You know.
Ye-in: But honestly, I don't think I could say that. Like that.
Jun-bin: I usually do. I have some single friends too.
Ye-in: So, if a single friend asks why they can't get a girlfriend, what do you say?
Jun-bin: I explain in detail that this and that part of their personality is a problem.
Jun-bin: I tell them to improve these parts before dating, trying to flirt, or getting set up.
Jun-bin: That's how I talk to them.
Ye-in: Then what does your friend say?
Jun-bin: When I talk, they understand. To them, I'm a hero.
Ye-in: [Everyone laughed in the radio studio.]
Ye-in: Ah, right. You're a hero.
Ye-in: Ah, this is difficult. So, Jun-bin thinks this is rude.
Jun-bin: Yes.
Ye-in: This insincere consolation.
Jun-bin: It's rude considering the person's situation.
Ye-in: I feel like I've lived a rude life. Kind of giving insincere consolations.
Ye-in: It could have been hurtful to them.
Jun-bin: That's right.
Ye-in: I'll try to be like Jun-bin in the future
Jun-bin: Considering the situation and talking like this.
Ye-in: Changing perspectives.
Jun-bin: Yes, yes, yes.
Ye-in: Nowadays, you're very popular, Jun-bin. Are you popular with girls around you in real life too?
Jun-bin: No.
Ye-in: Let's move on to part two and continue our discussion.
Jun-bin: Yes.
Ye-in: [Everyone laughed in the radio studio.]
Jun-bin: Is this not going out?
Producer: It's currently being broadcasted.
Ye-in: It paused for a moment.
Jun-bin: It stopped, this thing.
Ye-in: There was buffering.
Producer: It's just the screen.
Producer: Just refresh the page.
Producer: Should I get you more water?
Jun-bin: I have water.
Ye-in: Yes.
Producer: Ye-in is good at handling awkward transitions.
Ye-in: I've been surviving here for 10 years with that.
Ye-in: Yes.
Producer: About the "look in the mirror" comment earlier, Jun-bin's expression was
Jun-bin: My expression was caught earlier?
Ye-in: [Everyone laughed in the radio studio.]
Ye-in: I never say such things, but when you asked to give a reality check,
Ye-in: I mentioned looking in the mirror of the heart, insightfully
Jun-bin: You're good at wrapping things up.
Ye-in: I've made it this far with packaging.
Jun-bin: You're really good at this.
Ye-in: Hahahahaha
Jun-bin: Should you start a YouTube channel?
Ye-in: I tried YouTube, but it didn't work out.
Ye-in: [Everyone laughed in the radio studio.]
Ye-in: Can you appear on Jun-bin's YouTube channel?
Jun-bin: You can always come to mine.
Ye-in: Really?
Ye-in: Then can I get permission from the company and go?
Jun-bin: If the company gets involved, it's a bit
Ye-in: The company doesn't get involved, just asking the company, "Can I go?" like that
Jun-bin: If it's natural
Jun-bin: Then it's fine
Jun-bin: Without having to send a preview or anything, just naturally
Jun-bin: If you come to mine, we have to travel
Ye-in: Shall we go on a day trip?
Jun-bin: Yes?
Ye-in: On a day trip?
Jun-bin: That's not a trip, that's an outing.
Ye-in: [Everyone laughed in the radio studio.]
Ye-in: Because there might be people who find it hard to stay overnight
Ye-in: How about designing a date course for those people, for a travel date course?
Jun-bin: A date course?
Ye-in: A travel course.
Ye-in: [Everyone laughed in the radio studio.]
Ye-in: I can't seem to speak.
Jun-bin: It's no different from the story we just heard.
Ye-in: [Everyone laughed in the radio studio.]
Jun-bin: Am I the rude one for misunderstanding?
Jun-bin: You said it was a date course?
Ye-in: So, we're not dating, but we could design a travel date course for them,
Jun-bin: So, it's a travel date then.
Ye-in: On a day trip.
Ye-in: Wouldn't that be nice?
Ye-in: Ye-in is rude
Producer: Please return to page 6 for a moment.
Jun-bin: Are we starting right away?
Producer: Yes, we're starting.
Producer: We'll play the background music when you do the skit.
Ye-in: Yes....
Producer: Starting part two now.
Ye-in: You're listening to Jung Ye-in's Ten, I'm special DJ YengDi, Jung Ye-in,
Ye-in: Beside me is today's special guest, a man who seems smarter and more attractive due to his popularity,
Ye-in: GwakTube's Gwak Jun-bin, and we're conducting the "Champions League of Rudeness" segment.
Ye-in: This time, we're meeting a rudeness story brought to life through acting.
Ye-in: We've adapted a story from a lady, 'Anonymous Song'.
Ye-in: [I went on a date with a guy I met through a blind date and started dating after 2 weeks. We were still in the shy phase but enjoying thrilling dates.]
Ye-in: [He invited me over to his place, so I visited his apartment where he lives alone.]
Ye-in: [Jun-bin, can I come in?]
Jun-bin: [Yeah, come on in. Just sit there, I'm making delicious curry, so just wait a bit.]
Ye-in: [Okay, but it smells so good. Can I look forward to it? Hohohoho]
Jun-bin: [Of course, of course. Hahahahaha. It's all done. Here, enjoy. This is for you, my Ye-in.]
Ye-in: [Yeah, you too.]
Ye-in: [Mmm, wow, it's really delicious.]
Jun-bin: [Hahahahaha. Glad it suits your taste. Hahahahaha.]
Jun-bin: [Fart sound.]
Ye-in: [Huh? Didn't we just hear a strange sound?]
Ye-in: [Something broke, I heard it.]
Jun-bin: [I just farted. You must be comfortable around me, so it all came out. But it's an odorless fart.]
Jun-bin: [It's a fart, but there's no smell.]
Ye-in: [Oh? Oh, so you farted. You farted while we were eating curry. Hahahahaha.]
Jun-bin: [You finished your meal already, did you like it?]
Ye-in: [Yeah, it was really delicious. Jun-bin, you're great at cooking, the best, the best.]
Jun-bin: [Then, since I'm the best man, should we kiss now that we're bored? Come here.]
Jun-bin: [Come here.]
Ye-in: [Wait, wait, wait. You just ate curry, and there are still food particles in your teeth.]
Jun-bin: [So what? We're just going to kiss now. Come here and touch lips.]
Ye-in: [No, wait, wait, wait.]
Jun-bin: [What's with the wait? Just come here.]
Ye-in: You should kiss.
Ye-in: [That day, we ended up kissing and are still dating now, but opinions are still divided.]
Ye-in: [Honestly, even if we're a couple, isn't it a bit off to fart while eating?]
Ye-in: [And isn't it a bit off to kiss right after eating, with food particles still in your teeth? Isn't that rude?]
Ye-in: First, they acted as a couple.
Jun-bin: Wow, you're really good at this.
Ye-in: It was good, right?
Jun-bin: Me?
Ye-in: Didn't we do well?
Jun-bin: Ye-in, you're really good at this.
Ye-in: You too, Jun-bin.
Jun-bin: Really?
Ye-in: Yes.....
Ye-in: It felt so real.
Jun-bin: Me?
Ye-in: Yes...
Ye-in: [Everyone laughed in the radio studio.]
Ye-in: Hahahahaha
Ye-in: If a boyfriend and girlfriend actually fart while eating like this,
Ye-in: is it okay? Absolutely not okay?
Jun-bin: Well, I think the length of the relationship matters here.
Jun-bin: If it's around 100 days, probably not okay,
Jun-bin: but from 200 days, maybe it's acceptable.
Ye-in: So, in this case, being just 2 weeks into the relationship, it's out of the question?
Jun-bin: 2 weeks is definitely crossing a line, but
Jun-bin: I personally have severe nervous colitis.
Ye-in: What colitis?
Jun-bin: Nervous colitis.
Ye-in: Yes, yes, yes.
Jun-bin: So, when I'm with my girlfriend, I become very sensitive and tense, which makes me fart easily.
Ye-in: What do you do then? Do you hold it in?
Jun-bin: I ask for understanding. I have this condition; can you understand? And once they do,
Ye-in: Ah.
Jun-bin: the fart bombs start coming.
Ye-in: So, like once every 5 minutes?
Jun-bin: Not that often, once every 30 minutes.
Ye-in: Every 30 minutes?
Jun-bin: Yes, yes.
Ye-in: Deadly farts?
Jun-bin: But if a guy 2 weeks into the relationship has this kind of illness and asks for understanding, what do you think?
Ye-in: I'd totally understand; farting is, after all, a natural bodily function.
Jun-bin: Do you fart then, in front of your partner?
Ye-in: I've been in a relationship at such a young age that I don't remember.
Ye-in: [Everyone laughed in the radio studio.]
Jun-bin: You've never been in a relationship, have you?
Ye-in: No, I have, I have. I have been in a relationship.
Jun-bin: In elementary school?
Ye-in: In middle school.
Jun-bin: Ah, I see.
Ye-in: Because I debuted in high school.
Jun-bin: So you've never dated around that time.
Ye-in: Yes.
Ye-in: Yes, so I never really had the dilemma of farting around a boyfriend because, in middle school, boys don't really stay long enough for that to happen.
Ye-in: Uh, there's no such worry about farting or not since relationships weren't that long.
Jun-bin: I see.
Ye-in: Have you farted around your girlfriend before?
Jun-bin: I fart around anyone I'm dating.
Ye-in: Really? How soon?
Ye-in: I also did it around 2 weeks in, but I ask for understanding like this, not while kissing and farting,
Jun-bin: There are farts during kissing,
Ye-in: What if it smells bad while kissing?
Jun-bin: If I feel a fart coming, I don't kiss.
Ye-in: Ah.
Jun-bin: I've never made that mistake.
Ye-in: So multitasking doesn't work.
Jun-bin: I've never made that mistake where I'm about to fart and then start kissing. If my stomach hurts, I don't initiate physical contact.
Jun-bin: But we've been talking about disgusting stuff for too long.
Ye-in: Ah, but if not for me, would that peck even have been a topic? We did talk about pecks, right?
Ye-in: How do you feel about pecking without brushing first?
Jun-bin: Right after eating... But, you might not know since you haven't been in a relationship,
Ye-in: Yes
Jun-bin: it's the time when love's sparks fly, the first two weeks.
Jun-bin: You want to peck just from seeing each other's face, it's the time when skinship is most desired. Two weeks in,
Jun-bin: So, really, and she even accepted it, despite saying wait a minute, wait a minute,
Ye-in: Ah
Jun-bin: People who dislike it won't accept it, not at all.
Ye-in: Ah, that wait, wait, wait isn't a wait of dislike.
Jun-bin: Just pondering for a bit, wait wait wait.
Ye-in: Ah, I also kind of want to,
Jun-bin: Want to, but it's a bit dirty but still nice, so the person in the story went for the peck.
Ye-in: Yes
Jun-bin: So, it's a gray area.
Ye-in: Ah, gray area. Ah, if both parties are okay with it, then it should be fine.
Jun-bin: Yes
Ye-in: Right, if both are fine with it, I think it's like this,
Ye-in: Maybe it would be okay 10 minutes after eating? After eating and having some water.
Jun-bin: That's why, you know, when you're about to have skinship, you don't always brush your teeth,
Jun-bin: You don't say, 'I'll brush my teeth before we peck',
Ye-in: Right, right.
Jun-bin: So, whether you peck 10 minutes later or 1 minute later, there's always going to be some food residue,
Jun-bin: It's not like you're going to wipe it off with a tissue,
Ye-in: Right, right.
Jun-bin: So, I think as long as there's mutual understanding, it's an act that can be done.
Ye-in: Right, there's no correct answer in love. Commenters are asking, 'What if spinach gets stuck?'
Ye-in: 'What if you ate raw garlic?'
Jun-bin: I doubt the peck would be powerful enough to pull out spinach,
Ye-in: While pecking?
Jun-bin: Yes, but it's only the second week,
Ye-in: Right, not a vacuum cleaner.
Jun-bin: So, farting might be wrong in the second week, but pecking is somewhat forgivable then.
Ye-in: Ah, pecking is fine.
Jun-bin: From around two months, you'd start saying, 'Ah, it smells, don't do it', but since it's only two weeks,
Jun-bin: it's when love is really burning. You'd peck on the streets and such.
Ye-in: Have you ever pecked on the streets?
Jun-bin: Me? I don't think I have.
Ye-in: You haven't.
Ye-in: Ah, but it makes sense. Even if it's only been two weeks, if you really like each other, a peck is doable,
Ye-in: but farting might have been a bit shocking for the girlfriend.
Ye-in: But this, dividing it into manners or not, it's a physiological thing after all,
Jun-bin: Yes, it's a bit ambiguous.
Ye-in: It's ambiguous, but I think the reaction afterwards is what's important.
Ye-in: If, after farting, you act too smug like, 'Ah, it's just a fart', I'd be pissed, but
Ye-in: if you fart and then apologize,
Jun-bin: Ah, that would be too cute.
Ye-in: That would seem very cute, right?
Jun-bin: Yes, it was very cute.
Ye-in: [Everyone in the radio studio laughs.]
Ye-in: How about that feeling? Just resolving it to this extent.
Jun-bin: It seems totally forgivable.
Ye-in: Yes, the reaction, exactly.
Ye-in: Oh, I'm sorry.
Ye-in: Reaching a consensus to this extent.
Ye-in: [Everyone in the radio studio laughs.]
Jun-bin: Trying to put myself in that situation, I get it.
Ye-in: Yes, yes.
Jun-bin: The storyteller is innocent.
Ye-in: Right, this is innocent, innocent indeed.
Ye-in: It's not rude, finding a middle ground would be nice.
Ye-in: Let's move on to another story.
Ye-in: Back to that
Ye-in: It would be great if you, Jun-bin, could read the story from Yak-ing.
Jun-bin: [Yak-ing went on a trip with a friend, but the friend didn't bring any skin lotion.]
Jun-bin: [So, I lent mine, and throughout the week-long trip, my friend used my skin lotion.]
Jun-bin: [I thought they would buy their own, but they used my cosmetics the entire trip. Totally rude, right?]
Jun-bin: [Or am I being too petty?]
Ye-in: What do you think?
Jun-bin: This one's really tricky because for a week, it's not really a big deal for guys, we don't use much.
Jun-bin: A week's worth doesn't make much of a dent; it's like a scoop's worth.
Jun-bin: But still, I think I would've at least bought them dinner or something.
Jun-bin: So, it's a bit of a dislike from me.
Jun-bin: It's slightly disagreeable.
Ye-in: Disagreeable?
Jun-bin: Yes, yes, yes.
Ye-in: Women might use expensive skin lotions.
Ye-in: And many women are serious about skincare.
Ye-in: So if it was expensive, I probably would've bought my own lotion halfway through.
Jun-bin: There seems to be a gender difference here.
Jun-bin: For example, when I went to Cuba with Pani and Hong-chul, both didn't have skin lotion.
Ye-in: Oh, I see.
Jun-bin: Hong-chul's was confiscated, and Pani just doesn't use it.
Ye-in: Oh, manly.
Jun-bin: Yes, he just applies sunscreen diligently.
Ye-in: Yes.
Jun-bin: But I gave them mine, and it really didn't bother me at all.
Ye-in: Right, right.
Jun-bin: It's the mindset of, we're going to use it anyway, let's share.
Jun-bin: And in exchange, I receive a lot of happiness from traveling together.
Jun-bin: So, I've never had a problem with sharing skin lotion while traveling.
Ye-in: Hmm, I haven't either. Most women usually bring their own stuff.
Ye-in: I don't use expensive skin lotion, so I'm fine with giving it away for free.
Ye-in: Go ahead, use it. Being stingy about it is petty.
Ye-in: Especially if a friend forgot theirs, right?
Jun-bin: But there are people who deliberately don't bring things.
Jun-bin: I understand about the skin lotion, but when they don't bring other stuff...
Ye-in: Like what?
Jun-bin: Not bringing clothes.
Ye-in: Then they'd go around naked?
Jun-bin: Especially when traveling, there are many places with incompatible plugs.
Ye-in: Right.
Jun-bin: Many places don't use 220 volts, so they don't bring adapters and keep charging together.
Jun-bin: Then, "Hey, let me charge too," gets a bit annoying.
Ye-in: Right, right. They might have deliberately not brought it.
Jun-bin: Yes.
Ye-in: Because you, Jun-bin, are a travel expert.
Ye-in: They might think you'd have everything, so they don't bother.
Jun-bin: But I haven't really traveled with friends recently.
Ye-in: Just for broadcasting.
Jun-bin: Yes, yes. It's a bit sad, now that I think about it.
Ye-in: Let's do a one-day trip with friends.
Jun-bin: A trip with friends? A friendship trip?
Ye-in: A friendship trip.
Jun-bin: Oh.
Ye-in: Like, lowering my age a bit, maybe something fun and cheap domestically.
Jun-bin: Why should I build a friendship with Ye-in?
Ye-in: Right, you don't do that, no female friends.
Jun-bin: Why should I travel with a work colleague?
Ye-in: Oh, that's really attractive. I like that.
Ye-in: Oh, that's not bad.
Jun-bin: Shall we go on a trip then?
Ye-in: Not if it's like that, we won't go.
Ye-in: Oh, good, good. There's no friendship trip, do a workshop they say.
Jun-bin: A workshop, ah, I like workshops.
Ye-in: Yes, a workshop.
Jun-bin: Learned a good word.
Ye-in: Shall we all go on a workshop?
Jun-bin: Why should I? Why should I go with BaeTen's production team?
Ye-in: [Everyone laughs]
Ye-in: We're all a family, right?
Jun-bin: I only show up once a year.
Ye-in: Like a holiday, right.
Ye-in: Nice. This issue is not necessarily about manners but more about finding a consensus.
Jun-bin: Yes, I think a solution can definitely be found for this.
Ye-in: Yes, let's suggest at least one solution.
Ye-in: [Everyone laughs]
Ye-in: Let's read another story. Here's one from 'How Much Orange'.
Ye-in: [I went to an exhibition alone.]
Ye-in: [A couple asked me to take their photo.]
Ye-in: [After taking lots of photos for them, I was about to ask them to take one of me,]
Ye-in: [but as soon as they got their phone back, they said thanks and just left.]
Ye-in: [Isn't it manners to offer to take a photo for someone who's alone after they've taken yours?]
Jun-bin: This happens a lot when traveling abroad.
Jun-bin: But I've encountered many who don't offer to take a photo in return.
Jun-bin: It was always disappointing.
Jun-bin: Koreans are really good at taking photos.
Ye-in: Right.
Jun-bin: Foreigners often don't take good ones.
Ye-in: Really?
Jun-bin: They make your legs look short, though I have short legs.
Jun-bin: So even when I did get my photo taken, it wasn't great.
Jun-bin: But, on the topic,
Jun-bin: Offering to take a photo is more about being considerate than manners.
Jun-bin: It's sensible to ask, and we shouldn't condemn those without that sense as ill-mannered.
Ye-in: Right, right, that makes sense.
Ye-in: It seems more a matter of sensibility than manners.
Ye-in: But you travel alone often, right? How do you handle photos?
Jun-bin: I rarely take photos because I'm usually filming.
Ye-in: So how do you solve it?
Jun-bin: I don't really take many photos.
Jun-bin: Because the camera is always recording, everything is documented.
Ye-in: Yes.
Jun-bin: I don't take many photos, but when I do, I always ask foreigners.
Jun-bin: But they never turn out well.
Ye-in: Ah.
Jun-bin: No country takes photos as well as Korea.
Ye-in: In Korea, photos are taken just right, with toes aligned and legs looking longer.
Jun-bin: They make your legs look longer.
Ye-in: Right.
Jun-bin: They take good photos.
Ye-in: Yes.
Jun-bin: Foreigners make me look like a third of my height.
Ye-in: Ah.
Ye-in: Uh.
Jun-bin: Yes.
Ye-in: Shall we read the next story?
Ye-in: Here's one from 'Coco 38'.
Jun-bin: [I'm living with a friend.]
Jun-bin: [We rarely cook at home, so it takes a while to fill up the food waste bag.]
Jun-bin: [I suggested freezing it because of the smell,]
Jun-bin: [but my friend finds it too gross to keep it in the freezer and prefers leaving it outside.]
Jun-bin: [Which is more ill-mannered: Storing food waste in the freezer with food or letting it stink up the kitchen?]
Ye-in: This is really tough. What do you do normally?
Jun-bin: I bought a food waste disposer.
Ye-in: The one that grinds it into powder?
Jun-bin: It's the one that feeds it to microbes.
Ye-in: Wow, wow.
Jun-bin: Like keeping a pet, that's how I'm dealing with it.
Jun-bin: PaniBottle recommended it to me.
Ye-in: How is it? Did it improve your quality of life?
Jun-bin: I hardly put food waste in it.
Ye-in: Because you eat it all?
Jun-bin: Yes.
Ye-in: That's the best way.
Jun-bin: But I used to keep it in the freezer.
Jun-bin: What do you do?
Ye-in: I also keep it in the freezer.
Ye-in: It takes too long to fill up, so I put it in the freezer, but not directly.
Ye-in: I put the bag in another container and then freeze it.
Ye-in: My mom suggested this, and it works well, especially in the summer.
Ye-in: Flies gather quickly, and it smells really bad.
Jun-bin: But even in the kitchen, if you keep it in a container,
Jun-bin: it doesn't smell that bad.
Ye-in: Even at room temperature?
Jun-bin: Yes, but if you store it in the freezer in a container as mentioned,
Jun-bin: the smell really doesn't spread much.
Ye-in: This is tough to resolve, isn't it?
Jun-bin: It's not really about manners here.
Ye-in: A matter of preference?
Jun-bin: It's a matter of preference, but putting food waste directly in the freezer is a no-go.
Ye-in: Yes, yes.
Jun-bin: Keeping it in a container seems fine.
Jun-bin: This is really difficult.
Ye-in: You used to live off PaniBottle, right?
Jun-bin: I lived off him for about a week or two, and Pani lived at my place for about 4 months.
Ye-in: Why did that happen?
Jun-bin: I'm not really the type to live off others well, but Pani likes living with someone.
Ye-in: Ah, ah.
Jun-bin: Even though he could afford his own place, he stayed with us.
Ye-in: Ah, wanting to live together even if it means finding a place later.
Jun-bin: I hinted a lot, asking if he found a place yet.
Jun-bin: But he always said he would, staying longer than expected.
Ye-in: You must be close.
Jun-bin: Yes, we're like brothers.
Ye-in: Any incompatible habits?
Jun-bin: Everything was fine except for leftovers from broadcasting shoots.
Ye-in: Yes.
Jun-bin: He brings everything home.
Ye-in: PaniBottle does?
Jun-bin: Yes, a lot. Not that bringing things is bad, but he brings too much.
Ye-in: Everything.
Jun-bin: Yes, all sorts of things.
Jun-bin: He can't stand seeing anything go to waste, bringing home hotel amenities and anything that's free.
Ye-in: Yes, yes.
Jun-bin: As a result, our fridge was always full.
Ye-in: No space left.
Jun-bin: Yes, yes.
Ye-in: And when he brings stuff, he expects to share it.
Jun-bin: Yes, let's eat together.
Ye-in: Ah, let's eat together.
Jun-bin: Yes.
Ye-in: Interesting.
Jun-bin: I realized you can really bring that much stuff.
Ye-in: I leave everything behind.
Ye-in: I don't really bring things with me.
Jun-bin: I'm the same. I lose things if I'm holding them.
Ye-in: Wow, me too, exactly.
Jun-bin: How do we get along so well?
Ye-in: [Everyone laughs]
Ye-in: But really, living together is hard to reconcile.
Ye-in: It seems to be a matter of taste. This issue, above all, requires a conversation.
Jun-bin: Yes, yes.
Ye-in: To find a compromise.
Jun-bin: There are plenty of ways to solve this.
Ye-in: Yes, let's just give one solution.
Jun-bin: Search online for a container, like a 'Lock&Lock'. Oh, that's a brand name.
Jun-bin: Get a sealed container; it really doesn't smell much.
Ye-in: Good tip, seems like a good solution.
Jun-bin: Yes, yes.
Ye-in: Let's move on to the next story with this solution.
Ye-in: 'Squid Game' says, [I'm a very casual guy.]
Ye-in: [One day, I noticed my finger hair was too noticeable, so I borrowed an eyebrow razor from a colleague to trim it.]
Ye-in: [She got mad, asking why I used her eyebrow razor for that.]
Ye-in: [Honestly, I also trimmed some facial fuzz and slightly unshaven beard.]
Ye-in: [Is this really such bad manners?]
Jun-bin: Isn't that too much of a bad manner?
Ye-in: But I think it's okay.
Jun-bin: Are you just being contrary?
Ye-in: No, no, no, because
Ye-in: It's not like
Ye-in: he trimmed nose hair with it.
Jun-bin: But he used a female colleague's eyebrow razor to trim his finger hair.
Ye-in: Is that so?
Jun-bin: What I thought was,
Jun-bin: Did this person only do this kind of behavior?
Ye-in: Did he also use it for other purposes?
Jun-bin: No, I was worried he might have done other rude acts.
Ye-in: Like trimming armpit hair with it?
Ye-in: That would be really bad manners; you'd have to buy them a new one.
Ye-in: Or buy your own next time, but
Jun-bin: Isn't it not about hair?
Ye-in: Hmm, right, right, this is
Ye-in: Right, but finger hair isn't dirty, right?
Jun-bin: Is that so?
Ye-in: Yes, finger hair.
Jun-bin: I've never thought about it.
Ye-in: Trimming finger hair and just wiping it with
Ye-in: those small, like, alcohol swabs they used during COVID.
Ye-in: Wipe it with alcohol and say it's disinfected. Is that too much?
Jun-bin: But honestly trimming facial fuzz and beard with it?
Ye-in: Oh, did he trim that too?
Jun-bin: Honestly, along with a bonus of trimming here, thinking, "This much should be fine, right?"
Ye-in: Oh, also trimming here with the razor.
Jun-bin: Yeah, seeing what else he can get away with.
Ye-in: I think finger hair is okay, but
Jun-bin: But using it on facial hair and beard is too much.
Ye-in: Ah, from a needle thief to a cow thief.
Ye-in: Ah, then he might end up using it on armpits.
Ye-in: Actually, finger hair is fine for me.
Jun-bin: So, finger hair should have been stopped.
Ye-in: Ah, ah, that makes sense.
Ye-in: He should have been caught at finger hair.
Ye-in: But really, why is finger hair okay for me?
Jun-bin: Because that's just a pretense for actually wanting to trim his beard.
Ye-in: Ah, really seducing with the finger hair but actually going for the beard.
Jun-bin: Exactly. 'Devil's Plan.'
Ye-in: So, it was actually the face he was after, seducing with the finger hair.
Ye-in: So, what do we do? Is it bad manners?
Jun-bin: This person should probably reflect a bit, don't you think?
Ye-in: Right, just go to Olive Young next time, it's just a few thousand won.
Jun-bin: I recommend buying about ten of them.
Ye-in: Next time, buy your own or give one to the female colleague, especially since it's a sensitive item.
Jun-bin: Right.
Ye-in: Yes, just be a bit more considerate, thank you.
Jun-bin: Yes, yes.
SRT    .
```srt
Ye-in: Shall we read the next story?
Jun-bin: [This is a famous debate on the internet.]
Jun-bin: [Between Cheol-soo, who broke ten dishes while trying to help with the dishes, and Young-hee, who broke one dish trying to steal candy, who do you think is more mannerless?]
Ye-in: Ah, it's tough. 'Handdrip' sent us this one, what do you think?
Jun-bin: Wow, breaking ten is a bit much.
Jun-bin: If it was five, I'd say Cheol-soo did well, but ten, and there might be a difference in cost too.
Ye-in: Yes.
Jun-bin: Dishes are expensive.
Ye-in: Dishes are expensive.
Jun-bin: Yes, I didn't know until I started living alone, but dishes are that expensive.
Ye-in: They are expensive.
Jun-bin: But Cheol-soo is such a warm-hearted person.
Ye-in: Ten is a bit too much, according to the comments too.
Jun-bin: But Young-hee isn't exactly a thief, it was just one candy.
Ye-in: Ah, so is that action too cute? Is one candy forgivable?
Jun-bin: Ah, but it's similar to the finger hair thing.
Ye-in: Right, it's like going from a needle thief to a cow thief.
Jun-bin: If forgiven, one might even steal the safe at home.
Ye-in: Exactly. Right. Why steal? Just ask and eat.
Jun-bin: Exactly.
Ye-in: Why steal candy.
Jun-bin: I think Young-hee did wrong.
Ye-in: Me too.
Jun-bin: She needs to be caught.
Jun-bin: For Cheol-soo, we should actually praise him so he thinks, "I need to live more diligently like this," realizing that he can be forgiven for doing good deeds.
Jun-bin: And Young-hee, on the other hand, needs to be strictly taught not to steal again.
Ye-in: Yes.
Jun-bin: This seems like the right answer.
01:02
Ye-in: Right.
Ye-in: Exactly, this seems to be the right approach.
Ye-in: Stealing someone else's belongings is wrong. And the broken dishes are a sign from god.
Ye-in: It's a message saying, "Don't do such things in the future."
Ye-in: Letting everyone know by breaking a dish.
Ye-in: We'll wrap it up like this, everyone.
Jun-bin: Yes.
Ye-in: Let's summarize it like this.
Jun-bin: We wrapped it up nicely.
Ye-in: Yes, it fits well.
Jun-bin: It really fits well.
Jun-bin: We could do a segment together.
Ye-in: That fits well.
Jun-bin: Yes, so maybe we could do something once a month.
Ye-in: That sounds good.
Ye-in: Once a month, send Brother Seong-jae on a trip and just the two of us.
Jun-bin: The two of us could go on a trip and do a radio show outdoors.
Ye-in: Ah, just change the background completely.
Jun-bin: Ah, yes yes yes.
Ye-in: You said you don't travel with colleagues, right?
Jun-bin: Ah, no, I thought you were avoiding colleagues, so I said it's about friendship.
Ye-in: Ah, kind of like a workshop concept.
Jun-bin: Yes yes yes, you went to a workshop, and I just did something too.
Ye-in: [Everyone in the radio studio laughs.]
Jun-bin: I said that because of my image.
Ye-in: I know, I know.
Jun-bin: Yes yes yes.
Ye-in: What is Jun-bin lacking?
Jun-bin: Yes, what?
Ye-in: You're doing well.
Ye-in: 'Royal9083' [It was just me and my younger sibling at home this weekend.]
Ye-in: [I woke up first and cooked the only ramen we had at home.]
Ye-in: [Later, my sibling woke up, saw me eating ramen, and ordered jjajangmyeon for themselves.]
Ye-in: [How can they order delivery food without asking if I wanted some too?]
Ye-in: [Isn't this really mannerless?]
Jun-bin: That's so cute though.
Ye-in: You think it's cute?
Ye-in: What do you usually do? Do you ask people around you when you order something?
Ye-in: Do you usually order together?
Jun-bin: Yes, I do, but doesn't the person who sent this story sound a bit childish?
Ye-in: It is kind of cute.
Jun-bin: Seeing me eating ramen and eating jjajangmyeon alone.
Jun-bin: The tastes are similar, but ramen is delicious.
Ye-in: I'm a bit worse.
Ye-in: If my sibling is eating ramen, I ask for a bite.
Jun-bin: Do they give you a bite?
Ye-in: They give me a bite, my sibling is too kind.
Jun-bin: Can't you finish a whole jjajangmyeon?
Ye-in: I can't finish one.
Jun-bin: I thought so.
Ye-in: But I like to order multiple menus and eat them.
Ye-in: Even if I'm alone, I order a half-and-half set of jjajang rice and sweet and sour pork.
Ye-in: And I order jjamppong soup for 2,000 won extra and eat like that.
Jun-bin: But not to force it, but I also like to order various things because it often appears in my videos.
Jun-bin: I like to taste by ordering at least three things.
Ye-in: Especially with Chinese food, if one of the three, jjajangmyeon, jjamppong, or sweet and sour pork, is missing, I can't eat.
Jun-bin: Me too, me too.
Ye-in: [Everyone in the radio studio laughs.]
Jun-bin: Finding a new connection here.
Jun-bin: So, about this story.
Ye-in: Then, when we eat jjajangmyeon next time, let's eat together.
Jun-bin: Since you can't eat much.
Ye-in: Jjajangmyeon, jjamppong, and sweet and sour pork together.
Jun-bin: Just a bite of each, so it's great.
Ye-in: That sounds good, like we've found a jjajangmyeon mate.
Jun-bin: This friend too.
Ye-in: [Everyone in the radio studio laughs.]
Jun-bin: The sibling could have asked the brother if he wanted some.
Jun-bin: But there's often such squabbles between siblings.
Ye-in: Do you have them? I don't have a brother, so.
Jun-bin: I fought over such trivial things so much.
Ye-in: Do you have a brother?
Jun-bin: I have a brother, even over the computer, we fought fiercely over just 30 more minutes, even came to blows.
Jun-bin: Fought over one more minute of a game, fought so much.
Jun-bin: This can't be considered mannerless, it's just making siblings closer.
Ye-in: Right, they're just living their own lives. It's not like they're giving money.
Jun-bin: This is rather good. It's a common thing between siblings.
Ye-in: Ah, this is nothing.
Jun-bin: Royal9084 really just has a good brother, a good sibling, that kind of feeling.
Ye-in: Got a normal sibling.
Jun-bin: Too normal siblings.
Ye-in: Uh, yes. Good. This is more of a natural phenomenon than about manners or manners.
Ye-in: Yes, it seems okay. Ah, now I want to eat jjajangmyeon.
Jun-bin: Shall we eat jjajangmyeon together after this (end)?
Ye-in: Well, I have a performance tomorrow, so come watch my performance.
Ye-in: [Everyone in the radio studio laughs.]
Ye-in: Can you come to watch a colleague's performance?
Jun-bin: Yes?
Ye-in: At least that much.
01:06:33,200
Jun-bin: Yes.
Jun-bin: Good luck with your performance.
Ye-in: Is that okay? Alright, thank you.
Ye-in: Thank you.
Ye-in: Then, let's try one more story and finish with the next one.
Ye-in: There are a lot of stories here.
Jun-bin: Shall we pick one?
Ye-in: Shall we?
Jun-bin: Shall we talk about dieting?
Ye-in: Yes, shall we try?
Jun-bin: [One of my friends succeeded in dieting.]
Jun-bin: [And now, every time we meet, they talk in detail about exercise and diet.]
Jun-bin: [I'm not interested, so I just let it go in one ear and out the other.]
Jun-bin: [My friend is upset.]
Jun-bin: [Am I the mannerless one for not listening, or is my friend the mannerless one for only talking about uninteresting things?] KingGod General.
Ye-in: Oh, dieting, dieting.
Jun-bin: That friend keeps giving unsolicited advice on dieting, even to someone who isn't dieting.
Jun-bin: Because I've succeeded in dieting.
Jun-bin: I don't think this is a problem with dieting. There's always that one friend.
Jun-bin: When they succeed in something, they get obsessed.
Ye-in: The bragging friends?
Jun-bin: Too many friends who brag under the guise of giving advice.
Jun-bin: Many friends have succeeded in something.
Jun-bin: They come and give so much unsolicited advice, it's stressful.
Ye-in: I think so too.
Ye-in: If the other person is curious, you can talk about it, but unsolicited advice or tips are a bit mannerless.
Jun-bin: It's just bragging, not advice.
Ye-in: It's satisfying their own ego.
Jun-bin: By teaching, they can show off how great they are, so it's a huge mannerless act.
Ye-in: And it's very hard for the listener.
Ye-in: Because I'm not interested, but listening also uses my time.
Jun-bin: Speaking of which, I think I'm kind of like that.
Ye-in: Ah, when you succeed in something, do you brag like, "I really did well"?
Jun-bin: Not exactly "I really did well," but I do feel a bit upset if not acknowledged.
Ye-in: Hmm, can you give an example of how detailed you talk?
Jun-bin: It was really bad in elementary school.
Jun-bin: Around 4th grade, I ranked first in my class.
Ye-in: Ah, in studies?
Jun-bin: I didn't have the image of being smart in elementary school.
Jun-bin: Nobody acknowledged it.
Ye-in: Yes, ranked first?
Jun-bin: Yes, it was so upsetting.
Jun-bin: So, I couldn't just say, "Actually, I'm the top ranked," so I went home and cried.
Ye-in: To your mother?
Jun-bin: I always do that to my mom.
Ye-in: Saying I ranked first?
Jun-bin: Now I have so much to brag about, so I talk a lot.
Jun-bin: My mom seems to dislike it when I call now.
Ye-in: Ah, asking you to be quiet?
Jun-bin: If not my mom, who else would I talk to?
Ye-in: Ah, right.
Jun-bin: "I reached 1 million subscribers," who else would I tell?
Ye-in: But, ah, right, that's possible.
Ye-in: Somehow, I'm a bit shy about bragging.
Ye-in: I guess I haven't really had much to brag about in life, so I haven't really bragged much.
Jun-bin: You have so much to brag about.
Ye-in: Not really.
Jun-bin: Debuting as a girl group is already a huge brag.
Ye-in: Is it?
Jun-bin: Yes, it's everyone's dream, and the viewers are fans of Ye-in.
Ye-in: Ah, right.
Ye-in: Ah, it's like something irresistible even to maternal instincts.
Jun-bin: I do overdo it with my mom.
Ye-in: You can just get financial therapy for your mom.
Jun-bin: I always give financial therapy, but it's not enough.
Ye-in: Ah, I haven't been able to provide the financial therapy I wanted for my parents yet.
Ye-in: So maybe that's why I haven't really bragged to my parents yet.
Jun-bin: I haven't fulfilled it at all. I think there's no end to filial piety.
Ye-in: A hospital?
Jun-bin: I said it because I was being watched, mom is fully satisfied.
Ye-in: Well, anyway, about these diet success stories.
Jun-bin: It's not about dieting, but because this friend is bragging under the guise of advice, it's really mannerless.
Ye-in: Ah, yes, we need to talk honestly about this.
Jun-bin: Right, right.
Ye-in: I'm not interested in dieting.
Jun-bin: Don't be upset, you're the one at fault.
Ye-in: Talking like this, I think it's a bit mannerless.
Ye-in: Wow, we read a lot more stories than I thought.
Jun-bin: It really was the champions league.
Ye-in: Right.
Ye-in: Time has passed a lot, so after listening to the ads, it's time to say goodbye.
Jun-bin: Oh, so quickly.
Ye-in: Yes, we'll go listen to the ads first.
Jun-bin: Yes.
Jun-bin: Are we over time?
Production: Yes, we are over.
Production: After listening to the ads, both of you can wrap up.
Ye-in: Just like this?
Production: Yes, wrap it up and...
Ye-in: I heard today was fun, Jun-bin.
Jun-bin: Honestly, it was fun not because of me, but because you hosted so well.
Ye-in: Oh no, you were very entertaining.
Jun-bin: I didn't do much.
Ye-in: I'm kind of a fan myself.
Jun-bin: That's not quite the case.
Ye-in: [Everyone laughed.]
Ye-in: No, because, in my daily life, I fill the void with interesting YouTube videos.
Ye-in: And at one point, that void was filled by that
Jun-bin: 'Wheel Mouth'
Ye-in: 'Wheel Mouth' and
Jun-bin: 'Professor Gwak's Meal'
Ye-in: 'Professor Gwak's Meal'
Jun-bin: Oh, I regret not having you on the show.
Ye-in: You should invite me.
Jun-bin: Didn't they invite you?
Ye-in: No.
Jun-bin: It was tough to get guests back then.
Ye-in: Will you plug me in next time?
Jun-bin: I don't have that power, but
Ye-in: As a guest, as a guest.
Jun-bin: As a guest, I do have some influence.
Ye-in: Yeah, I want to speak up as a guest.
Jun-bin: But the important thing is, I've already left that show.
Ye-in: You're not doing it anymore?
Jun-bin: Yes, yes.
Ye-in: Why?
Jun-bin: I'm currently doing two new programs there.
Ye-in: You're doing another one? But 'Wheel Mouth', you're doing 'Wheel Mouth' again?
Jun-bin: 'Wheel Mouth' has been handed over and is still going on.
Jun-bin: If it's going well, you can't keep doing the same thing.
Jun-bin: So they are still doing fun talk shows.
Ye-in: I'm really grateful for having been a friend who shared my emptiness.
Jun-bin: They are still doing it, so watch 'Waffle'. Although I'm not appearing anymore, it's still fun.
Jun-bin: Please show a lot of love.
Ye-in: I'll keep watching your activities, Jun-bin.
Jun-bin: Are you going to watch 'Devil's Plan' when you get home?
Ye-in: Yes, of course.
Jun-bin: Yes.
Ye-in: I'll see how dirty you played.
Ye-in: Am I going to be like, "What? The guy I was just with, what's with his character?"
Jun-bin: Where are you originally from?
Ye-in: I'm from Incheon.
Jun-bin: Ah, Incheon? But you often have a Gyeongsang-do accent.
Ye-in: Ah, I kind of have that. Yes, I've heard that a lot.
Jun-bin: I'm purely from Gyeongsang-do.
Ye-in: Right. I think dialects are really a talent.
Ye-in: Kind of like a special skill.
Jun-bin: Is that right? (Gyeongsang-do accent)
Ye-in: Is that right? (Gyeongsang-do accent)
Ye-in: I'm kind of drawn to people who can speak dialects.
Ye-in: It's like the last time.
Jun-bin: I ended up wrapping up the last part.
Ye-in: Right.
Ye-in: It's an honor.
Production: We've listened to the ads.
Ye-in: All the ill-mannered texts introduced in today's Non-dating Champions League will receive a 'Sunrise Portable Lantern'. Congratulations to everyone.
Ye
-in: GwakTube's Gwak Jun-bin,
Ye-in: how was your time with YengDi instead of BaeDi on YengTen?
Jun-bin: I wish YengDi would continue, it was so fun and enjoyable.
Jun-bin: It was very comfortable, and I had a great time.
Ye-in: I had a great time too.
Ye-in: Actually, this will probably be my last time as a radio DJ.
Jun-bin: The honor of being the last one with me seems to add more meaning to it.
Ye-in: Ending is important, right?
Ye-in: I think it's great that we ended it so well with Jun-bin, and I feel really good about it.
Ye-in: And if there's another opportunity, I'd like to visit again as a special DJ.
Ye-in: Yeng...
Ye-in: Yeng DJ.
Ye-in: Wrapping up here, the last song will be 'You to Me, Me to You' by Jatanpung. We'll turn off the lights with this song. Dream with Ye-in.
Production: Good work, everyone.
Ye-in: You've worked hard.
Jun-bin: You've worked hard.
Ye-in: BaeTen is a radio show, but listening... it matches well with watching. That's the feeling.
Jun-bin: Did I use the expression watching? Did I?
Ye-in: I did. Just now.
Production: There are many viewers, too.
Production: But you should listen to BaeTen.
Ye-in: Right. BaeTen is for listening.
Jun-bin: Listening, yes.
Ye-in: It was really fun today.
Ye-in: Jun-bin.
Jun-bin: It would have been much stronger if it was an internet broadcast.
Ye-in: But since this is SBS public radio.
Jun-bin: I didn't hold back, though.
Ye-in: Really?
Ye-in: Is this the level of YouTube?
Jun-bin: Yes. Just like I usually do.
Jun-bin: I only held back on saying "masters of flirting" once.
Ye-in: I saw that. You swear a lot. Like using vulgar language.
Ye-in: So, that travel show, 'Marble World'
Jun-bin: 'Marble World'.
Ye-in: 'Marble World'. That game. 'Marble World'.
Ye-in: I watched one, and you kept
Ye-in: using broadcast-unfriendly words. The PD
Jun-bin: It's all acting. Acting.
Ye-in: Acting? Ah. Acting.
Ye-in: Right. Acting.
Jun-bin: I reflected a lot after watching.
Ye-in: You don't notice when you're using them, but when you see yourself...
Ye-in: You think, "I should fix this."
Ye-in: What are you doing now?
Jun-bin: Going to sleep. Now.
Ye-in: Going home to sleep?
Jun-bin: Yes. Yes.
Ye-in: Do you usually go to bed early?
Jun-bin: No. I play LoL and then sleep.
Ye-in: Ah, LoL.
Jun-bin: Yes.
Jun-bin: Is this still going on?
Ye-in: Yes.
Jun-bin: [I really enjoyed 'Busan Country Boy'. Thanks, GwakTube.]
Ye-in: [Everyone laughed.]
Ye-in: You've worked really hard.
Ye-in: Let's take a photo before you go.
Ye-in: It's hot.
Jun-bin: Is that a phone?
Production: No, it's a film camera.
Production: Brought it to take pictures.
Production: Come here for a photo.
Production: One, two, three.
Production: One more time.
Jun-bin: Will you give me the printed photo?
Production: Yes, we'll give it to you.
Jun-bin: I need to hang it at home.
Ye-in: [Everyone laughed.]
Ye-in: You've worked really hard.
Jun-bin: You've worked hard.
Production: You've worked hard.
Ye-in: Visit us again next time.
Jun-bin: You've worked hard.
Ye-in: Bye.
Ye-in: See you in the live broadcast, everyone.
Production: Shall we end it?
Production: Just a moment.
Production: Just turning off the sound.
Production: We'll end it at 55 minutes, just keep it going like this.
Production: It's still rolling, sis.